Hey
Speaker 1: guys, welcome to the channel. It's me Colin, Project Constitution. Joining me are my guest hosts, as usual, Kelvia, conservative, KFC Campbell. And we have a great show for you today. We have two very special guests that we want to introduce you guys to. We have the independent candidate, which actually, what is your party called again? Your actual name is the...
No
Speaker 2: labels. So no labels independent. Yeah.
Speaker 1: labels party. Okay. So, yeah. So we have Terry, Terry and Horahan, right? Yep. Okay. Of the no labels party, she's running for Arizona governor.
And
Speaker 3: then
Speaker 1: we have her running mate with us as well today, which is Angela Mohan, correct? Yes,
you
Speaker 4: got it right.
Speaker 1: Okay, good.
And
Speaker 1: we're just going to get into a little bit about
how they
Speaker 1: got started into it. I think Terry has a great story for why she decided to get involved in politics. She is not a career politician. She is not
Speaker 5: taking any special interest money, not taking any PAC money, and also has vowed to investigate Turning
Speaker 6: Point, which is something that I was very, very supportive of.
Speaker 6: So when I saw that, I was like, I definitely want to interview her.
So we
Speaker 6: have her on a show and we're going to jump right
Speaker 7: into it.
Speaker 8: Thanks.
You want me to
Speaker 8: start? We're so glad to
Speaker 9: have you here.
Yeah,
Speaker 10: sorry. We're so glad to have you here.
Speaker 11: You're a refreshing, you're a breath of fresh air. You know, we're taking a little bit of a break from Democrat, Republican, red and blue, you know, and we have a new refreshing face. So I hear you're an Arizona native. So I'm going to give it to you and tell us about yourself and how you got involved
and all the things. Yeah, thank
Speaker 12: you. And it went out just for a minute. I don't know if that was my screen or
Speaker 13: everyone's, but
yeah.
Speaker 13: thank you so much the uh for having us and uh we are neither one of us are career
Speaker 14: politicians angela and i so uh my background is i've been in arizona my whole life and i just shared stories that you know paula was my high school right down the street uh from me now which i live in glendale still so uh glendale i am born and raised still live in glendale a mother of two young boys six and seven both in public school
Speaker 14: uh, engaged to their father. And I am, um, so I, I start my story back 20, 18 years ago when I was 23 years old, got sober drugs and alcohol, gave my life to Christ. And I'm a Christian. And I, um, and I say that because it kind of leads into my story today, right? I say that because it was a pivotal moment in my life when, uh, I changed from, I went towards helping people. My life became, I earned a master's degree I
Speaker 14: became a licensed therapist. I'm an LPC. My focus is trauma. So EMDR, trauma therapist, PTSD is my specialty. I also do an animal assisted therapy. And then I earned a PhD in 2018 for counselor education. So I, you know,
so I
Speaker 14: focused my life on just helping people. And, and my telling my whole, like, just kind of how I got here to governor, would you like
to,
Speaker 15: Yeah, I mean, if you have any history in politics, like what your thoughts used to be to vote for
Speaker 17: Trump, you know, any of it. Yeah. OK, perfect. So I'll tell you how I got here. So 2017,
Speaker 13: my story is I started a company, Terry's Health Services. It's still around today.
Speaker 18: Counselor, I grew it from one person, which is myself, to 250 by 2023. We served throughout Arizona, 30 cities, over 39
Speaker 14: counties throughout, you know, corner to corner.
Speaker 14: corner, psychiatric medical behavioral health.
Then one
Speaker 14: day, 922-2023, about 11 a.m. etched in my mind, I got a call from an employee that said, Terry, we're on the Medicaid suspension list, essentially for what I knew that to be for an allegation of fraud. I knew we
Speaker 13: didn't commit fraud, right? My life from that moment has changed forever. And what should have taken 30 days
Speaker 14: to get off this list that they do to providers in the state of Arizona, thousands are going through this right now.
Speaker 14: it took me two years and seven days to clear my name i had experts in my company i had people report that there was no fraud waste abuse um but outside of uh despite that right um filing a against a software company that that this occurred under um which i can't say the name of it because it's in
Speaker 13: litigation
but you know uh
Speaker 13: two years and seven days and my company demolished 19 employees and in that fight um
Speaker 13: really, in 2024, I started reaching out to legislators. I actually ran into one at an event. She came up to me. Her name is Deborah Nardozzi. She was a state senator at the time. She's not now. She just lost at the race. But she introduced herself to me, and that was my start in politics. She didn't know who I was. I didn't know who she was, but I asked for a meeting. She was very kind. She is very kind. And I
Speaker 13: I said, absolutely. Thank you. And I met her. She believed me. She helped me. And then a year goes by, I'm working independently with access away from lawyers at that point. I still have lawyers. And then they terminate me, keep all my money, you know, over a
Speaker 14: million dollars. And that's when I started speaking out because I was in August. It was actually August 3rd of 2025. I started social media. And
like
Speaker 14: speaking
Speaker 18: out and about my story about what happened to me because thousands of providers in the state of Arizona and throughout our nation really I know it's happening other places uh it's happening to and right now there's just providers are being and I'm not you know some people are like oh you want to free the people who have committed fraud no if people have committed fraud then they deserve to be you know
Speaker 18: prosecuted and go to prison okay but we also have a dual issue here uh there are providers that have been on these lists that may have committed fraud that are not being indicted for years so they're running around the community what are they doing right so we don't have quick enough prosecutions this is where i get into due process right and my and why i attached uh really
when
to the
Speaker 18: charlie kirk assassination you know charlie kirk died september 10th we all know that and i had just started speaking out august 3rd of 25 and when i started speaking out i spoke out against the medicaid provider or people vanessa templeman i don't care i'll name them julie colton rebecca hernandez uh jenna pry all these people katie hobbs
Speaker 18: Chris Mays. I named people, right? It was my experience, but I also know these people, their inactions are harming people, inactions. And then I started to be retaliated against. They filed to try to silence my speech. They filed an injunction of harassment. Julie Colton filed an injunction of harassment.
Speaker 18: um right after she saying that i would i i she's i scared her so much like the uhc killer that's what she told the judge well if a government official says to a judge uh this person is talking out against me and i'm scared because she's you know the uhc killing just happened mind you i never even contacted this woman she just didn't want me to tell the truth about
her and um
And she
Speaker 19: that's after she she calls my executive board director, Toby Zavala, who I'll name her too. I've named her many times. She's I'm a licensed professional counselor. She they
Speaker 18: called my executive board and wanted me to, you know, take down my social media. They try to she sent me an email to extort me and say take down your social media or I'll open board complaints on your license.
I had a
Speaker 18: lawyer involved at that point and he said, no, uh, this is free speech. She can keep talking. Well, within two weeks, I got four board complaints by, uh, access employees, uh, the, their family members, Vanessa Templeman's sister, you know,
Speaker 19: like, uh, it was insane. Uh, I filed a lawsuit against Ford Weaver health. It's still in place. It's in the appellate court right now. Uh, those were
Speaker 20: finally dismissed. Okay. Not, but I had to go through a psychological evaluation
Speaker 20: which I passed. I
Speaker 21: mean, it's just like, yeah, it was just insane. It's pretty requisite to running. Well,
Speaker 19: there you go. I mean, I mean, you know, I think they were pissed. It came out clean as the
Speaker 18: whistle, but anyway, it wasn't, it was a loophole to try to, you know, continue to try to silence my speech, but yeah.
You
Speaker 18: know, it really is a God moment, a God story of me being here today. Really, it is. I believe I was called here.
Speaker 14: You know, some people think that's a crazy statement. Some people say they don't. You know, I'm for separation of church and state. When I say that, despite being Christian, I don't take money or pack money or
Speaker 22: influence or endorsements from
Speaker 23: churches, despite being part of a Christian organization.
Speaker 23: I go to CCB. So despite being part of the church, unlike my other opponents that certainly do.
So
Speaker 13: here I am, guys. I won my primary. Everyone said in the media and
Speaker 18: everything else didn't think I had a bright star in front of me.
But I
Speaker 18: told them from the start I was going to win the race,
and I
Speaker 18: was going to do it without a lot of money.
And
Speaker 18: they said, I'm full of it. So my party got behind a multimillionaire, Hugh Lytle. He spent over a million dollars in the race for the primary. He didn't debate me. I did a Q&A. You know, he thought he had it in the bag and then I kicked his butt in the election. And, you know, and that's the example. And I.
Speaker 18: went on the news
Speaker 14: and, you know, got invited for a lot of media and we do and I both do a lot of media and podcasts and those things. Mainstream media is interesting, right? It's an interesting little, little thing that's happening in our state and across the nation here. But, um, but yeah, that's my, you
Speaker 13: know, I'm here today. I believe we're going to win. I wouldn't be here if I didn't believe that. Um, and I, we work hard every single day. Um, and I, we work hard every single
Speaker 14: day.
to
Speaker 14: make Arizona a better state for us all and to stop the corruption. So when Ryan, who is probably listening now, I imagine, but had
Speaker 13: reached out to you, Colin, he and I connected a few months ago and this became part of I could get behind this because
I've
Speaker 13: been talking out
Speaker 14: against TPSA since, and I'll go back to the day that Kirk was assassinated, right? I did a reel on that day. And I said, this is, I had just learned about him when that happened.
Speaker 18: And
I, it
Speaker 18: really hit me hard because I was speaking out only for about six weeks. And I'd already had all of that retaliation occur to me. And obviously not at the level he experienced, obviously it was a horrible, but I thought, wow, this free,
Speaker 18: speech man this is uh incredible right regardless of people like him or don't like him he he got killed for you know for the things he believed in and the things that he was speaking and chose to do and i just um it's really and and the
Speaker 14: fact is that there's a lot of issues coming out and have come out regarding tp usa
i found it
It
Speaker 14: was quite alarming that they had the tent there at the memorial. I didn't go to the memorial, but in Arizona, they had pictures of the actual tent that was there is my presumption and belief that that was the actual tent and people were able to take pictures under it. And I thought that was bizarre.
And
Speaker 14: the
Speaker 24: microphone and the
Speaker 18: microphone was sold. And, and then they were selling just a few days after I thought it was disgusting. They had, they were selling
Speaker 19: mobile, you know, mobile services on his actual show to Charlie Kirk show. I mean, under his name. And so,
you know, I'm a
Speaker 19: trauma therapist, work with a lot of victims and a lot of people that
Speaker 18: have been
Speaker 18: uh, had tremendous things happen to them. And I, I do also realize that as Christians, we, we experienced death differently, but there's something just very odd here. Um, and I, obviously it's all alleged in, uh, in, in this area and, you know, we can't, I don't know,
but
Speaker 25: I'm for due process. And, and I think
that that's
Speaker 25: not occurring here in this case. So
I'm really,
Speaker 26: I'm really glad to
Speaker 27: hear that. And, um,
it's
Speaker 27: nice that you know we're just we're delving in you know to Arizona politics and turning point USA turning point action is obviously a huge part of Arizona politics um so you had never heard of
Speaker 28: Charlie Kirk before his
Speaker 29: death no no I didn't
Speaker 19: know
Speaker 28: yeah so I
Speaker 19: was not real political honestly my whole life um up until about two years ago you know people I was
Speaker 18: always a Democrat that doesn't mean anything to me people are like oh you're a Democrat I'm like well it doesn't mean anything to me.
Speaker 18: Arizona, a lot of most people don't know about politics. They keep it pretty silent. Right. You have to really dig and know talking to Colin about that. My parents were Democrats, so I was Democrat. I mean, it was I voted every year, but it was just it wasn't that, you know, I didn't think a lot of people are this way. Then when I ran for governor, the first I changed to Republican to run Republican first for 30 days, I did that. And the pull of the the ideology of the party was very difficult
Speaker 14: for me in which I.
Speaker 14: didn't want to be a part of so i went to no labels or it's under the in arizona there's four independent parties and there's
independent you
Speaker 25: can register as independent no party unaffiliated or no labels it's all the independent umbrella in arizona and so i ran under the no
Speaker 23: labels angela is uh registered independent um so
but again
Speaker 23: under the same umbrella
would you
Speaker 30: consider yourself i mean you mentioned
you
Speaker 30: Oh, sorry, Colin. I
Speaker 1: actually, I love your underdog story. I actually have a video. I love to show the video real quick from the news, actually, because I think I want to highlight the fact that you, you know, that your opponent had spent millions of dollars in campaigning against you. And you won basically out of pure grit, you know, out of pure grassroots effort.
Speaker 1: Because you were on the ground there, actually visiting these people, actually talking to them, you know, hearing their concerns. You had the same concerns. You know, you felt
what, you
Speaker 1: know, you were experiencing what these people were feeling. Yes. Yeah.
And
Speaker 1: they could see that, you know, and they could see that you're not a politician. You're you're the like the ultimate underdog. And I love that about you.
Speaker 32: Yeah,
Speaker 33: that's unheard of. That's almost unheard of these days just to go based off of grassroots without donors or APAC
or
Speaker 34: whatever. That's very impressive. Yeah, I'd love to see the clip.
Speaker 35: It's Julie Spilsbury out there Who is right now Oh, that's the wrong one, sorry
Speaker 36: It's the one for later One
Speaker 38: second That's the
Speaker 39: one I got for later Sorry about that
Speaker 39: I got all my tabs pulled up here. I got the wrong one pulled up. I was
Speaker 40: like, wow, I was on this one and didn't see this one.
All right, this is
Speaker 41: the one that we wanted. Okay.
Here we go. The biggest
Speaker 42: surprise during the primary election was an upset victory by a no-labels candidate for governor. Therapist Terry Herhan defeated a multimillionaire once
Speaker 43: hailed a potential independent governor of Arizona.
Speaker 44: news journalist and square off modern.
Speaker 44: Moderator Bram Resnick
Speaker 45: talked with Hurahan today and asked her why the No Labels campaign is filled with Republican references. I want to
start with the fact
Speaker 46: that I don't have any political background. I think that's what we need in politics today.
Speaker 47: 41-year-old licensed therapist Terry Hurahan finds herself neck deep in Arizona politics right now.
I
Speaker 48: do hard things. I take on big challenges.
Speaker 49: Millionaire healthcare executive Hugh Lytle was no match
for her.
Speaker 49: in the contest for the No Labels Party nomination for governor.
Speaker 50: In 2022, did you vote for Carrie Lake or Katie Hobbs for governor? You vote for Katie Hobbs in 2022?
Speaker 51: I've made that very clear. Less clear is what No
Speaker 47: Labels means to Hurran, a lifelong Democrat, she says. Her campaign sign mimics the look,
Speaker 49: colors, and graphic style of President Donald Trump's signs. Hurran's positions reflect Republican statements. And a candidate profile filed with the Secretary of State,
Speaker 49: says Terry Ann Hurahan is stepping forward as a candidate for governor of Arizona, a conservative
Speaker 52: voice for faith, family, and freedom. You say you are a conservative.
I,
Speaker 53: it's, conservative is...
Speaker 52: Are
Speaker 49: you a conservative?
Speaker 53: I'm not a Republican.
Speaker 49: Hurahan will join Democratic Governor Katie Hobbs, Republican Congressman Andy Biggs, and Green Party nominee Risa Lombardo on the November ballot for governor.
Speaker 49: lombardo and hurihan could be spoilers you can now watch square off on fridays and sundays catch us on 12 news at 12 30 p.m friday and 8 a.m sunday or watch us on the 12 news street
so yeah i mean i i
Speaker 54: absolutely love that i
Speaker 5: mean you absolutely just crushed in that election 100 percent um and the other thing is
And I
Speaker 5: like that they press you on. So are you a Republican? Why the labels, honestly? Most of us
Speaker 1: now are to the point where
we don't want
Speaker 1: labels. We're tired of it. We're all to the point now where both the Republicans are corrupt, the Democrats are corrupt, and we're tired of it. The two-party system is broken.
It's
Speaker 1: you know, it's no good anymore. We need somebody who is going to go in there and straighten up both sides, going to get rid of the corruption on both parties.
Speaker 55 (higher-pitched voice): Yeah, I agree. And that's, you know, and that was my you know, I think he did
Speaker 56 (higher-pitched voice): that for for.
Speaker 56 (higher-pitched voice): views right which it's like
Speaker 13: you know the there was no way I mean somebody made that emblem for me regarding my so my picture in those but I just thought it was interesting right it's like okay the flag is only a Republican can use the flag or you know the color red I mean let me write this down right what what can I not use according to and that's the thing that people need
to
you
Speaker 13: know, I try to help people understand, right. It's not a people question, what's an independent viewpoint.
Speaker 18: And I think in Arizona, we have to remember that over one third of us are registered independents here and in our
Speaker 57: state at least. And so we do not have to blend in. We are constantly told that we have to blend into one of the party systems.
Speaker 57: And the fact is, is that we don't have to independent is truly and I have
Speaker 13: rejected even my party's interview for endorsement to, you know, in the I'm very much like I just want to be for the
Speaker 18: people. Right. Because what's happening is.
is
Speaker 18: really, really harming our state. And I think for people
Speaker 57: listening, whether you're in Arizona or not,
one of
Speaker 57: the things I'm trying to help people understand regarding TPUSA is they're headquartered in Arizona.
Speaker 18: And I'm particularly, it's scary to think about their influence in our politics, not just nationwide, but particularly in Arizona. And why Arizona governor here is really important for those who really
Speaker 57: care about the movement
Speaker 57: um against turning point usa and wanting due process and this movement that is important right that ultimately if if trial or trial tyler robinson is not guilty which he has said he's not guilty
he uh you
Speaker 57: know and he's
Speaker 57: sentenced and he's found guilty and he's really not guilty where does
Speaker 13: that uh you know how fair is that process you know and some of the things coming out regarding i just recently watched something on the woods and finance he did a thing regarding tyler robinson's boyfriend and the money that paid off his home
um
Speaker 57: shortly after. I mean, it's just very odd, all these things. You know, again, I can't say A plus B equals C, but again, they need to be looked at. And in Arizona, it's a pivotal time
Speaker 23: for an Arizona governor to really take the reins and to do some audits on this huge organization that's affecting our community and our state or our nation.
I'm
Speaker 27: really happy to hear you say these things because, you know, Charlie's biggest thing was free speech. I know. Now, now, if you like I make the joke all the time, if you drive past headquarters, it looks like a compound and they treat it as a compound. It's all gated up. There's no free speech. I clearly lost my job because of free speech.
Speaker 27: Yeah, it's crazy. But the fact that you even bring up due
Speaker 59: process, I think Charlie would be rolling in his grave because Turning Point as a whole has completely overlooked the due process and innocent until proven guilty. And they've just gone straight for the jugular. They have no problem with this young man facing the death penalty.
Yeah.
they
Speaker 27: have no they they're more upset that you would criticize Erica Kirk which we don't have to get into but you know they're more they're more concerned
Speaker 60: with that than this young man who's facing the death penalty yeah and yeah they just completely you know I'm sure you're you know the UVU post-action report just came out recently and it was yeah
it's
Speaker 62: very damning towards turning
point
Speaker 59: and their role that security played
Speaker 59: September 10th yeah and you know
yeah and
Speaker 63 (higher-pitched voice): Angela I don't know Angela if you want to kind
of say
Speaker 63 (higher-pitched voice): who you are because your background is for is investigation yeah
I was like
Speaker 64: oh no here
Speaker 65: we go we'll pass it over
Angela Harold
Speaker 65: Mohan
Speaker 4: and I grew up in the
Speaker 66: Midwest actually but came to ASU ultimately go Devils fear the
fork
Speaker 67: and I was here for some time left Arizona
Speaker 67: went to 45 different countries and ultimately came back here because I'm a firm believer that this is one of the best places in the world. Spent some time in D.C. near your home there, Colin, in Maryland. But during that time, I was actually working for the U.S. Department of State as a special agent in diplomatic security, so under the umbrella of the Foreign Service. So talk about very apolitical on many levels, working with different nations and different cultures and having different experiences. Yeah.
But
Speaker 68: coming back to Arizona was important to me. My husband at the time was serving
Speaker 67: as a trooper medic, rescue medic in Arizona for DPS, our state police here. And he was ultimately killed in the line of duty. So I became a widow
Speaker 68: overnight with two very young children. So on some levels, I could look at Erica and say,
okay,
I get
Speaker 68: some of the things and I don't get a lot of the other things and we all take different directions when tragedy and adversity, you know, is presented to us, we all go in different directions.
Speaker 67: So I ultimately became a massive advocate for public safety here in Arizona and ran one of our largest nonprofits that supports police, fire, corrections here in the state of Arizona.
Speaker 68: and grew it tremendously over the course of an additional 10 years. So now you've got about a decade or two decades worth of what I've been doing. And after leaving there, I it wasn't long after anyway, Terry calls me randomly out of the blue. I don't know Terry. And she says, I'd like to meet you and I'd like to consider you for a lieutenant governor. And after hearing her story and hearing her adversity and seeing her passion, I was like, I can identify with that.
Speaker 68: Because
Speaker 67: during that chapter, after my late husband was killed, I became this massive advocate and I was like, there are things that need to be changed. I went ahead and presented several bills to our legislature here and was able to get three of those bills passed into law and I was very, very just humbled to be able to do that. And
Speaker 68: it was...
It
Speaker 68: was, it's obviously very fulfilling, but especially when you're doing things for the right reasons. So when Terry is like, I want to fix some things, I'm gonna run for governor. I mean, you could just go ahead and you can fix some laws, you could do some vestiges, or you'd run for governor. So I was like, hey, go get them. Like, I'm in, like, however we can do this to fix the process, to get involved, to address the concerns that we have, I think is,
is
Speaker 68: absolutely what we're supposed to do as servants. And I am not a career politician, as I mentioned. If anything, I was a government employee and a profit employee. So as a government employee, I know, I think it's perfect too. Just because, again, I'm tired of them yelling and lying about each other. I mean, on both sides and it's just disheartening. And the mailbox is full of just garbage.
Speaker 68: You know, you don't know what to believe. You don't know what's true. I have like 30 pieces. I'm just collecting them just for fun now. I mean, I like 30 pieces that I got like three days ago. Anyway, my point is I, yeah, I worked as an investigator for, like I said, nearly a decade. And then actually as a contract investigator for about another decade after that. And I recognize that if you need to, number one, you always ask the questions.
Ask
Speaker 68: the questions. No one should ever shut you out. If they're shutting you out and they're not answering the questions, there's probably a reason for that too. You'll get, they're gonna get their questions answered. It's just that simple. And obviously there's a jurisdictional component here, right, you've got Utah, you've got Arizona. I mean, Utah, that is a completely different animal. They're working on a homicide. They're trying to get to the answers on that homicide.
Speaker 68: But then that investigative component when it comes down to Arizona and what Terry could do as the potential governor here. It's important because there is oversight and transparency needed and people just say TPUSA. But as we all know, that's actually multiple.
Speaker 68: entities and they're all separate entities. So you've got TPUSA, you've got the nonprofit, the 501 component, obviously I'm very familiar with that. I'm very familiar with the reporting requirements and how they need to make sure they're maintaining their functional expenses and how they balance salaries versus what is considered a program. I mean, there's a lot of different components there that I find fascinating, but then it's like, where also do they support? Where also do they give their money
to?
Speaker 68: And if you look at TPUSA as a whole, now you're looking at I think maybe even five entities, there's a little bit of supporting each other in that process. And I think that oversight, transparency is 100 percent required, and no one should ever shy away from that. They should lean into that. They should be giving us, giving the community and interacting with the community in ways that's going
Speaker 69: to help them basically move forward.
Speaker 70: Yeah. Wow.
Speaker 1: Yeah. And and, you know, Tyler Tyler Boyer in particular is one of those people that likes to ride the line of the gray area and turning point in particular likes to move towards less transparency and trying to hide and obfuscate how all those different entities connect with each other and where the money flows and how they how they go to the candidates
and
Speaker 1: And honestly, I feel like they are breaking laws in doing that and, you know, we need to get transparency to be able
Speaker 6: to, you know, to look in their books to be able to tell, you
know.
Speaker 72: Yeah. Yeah. And it's it's it's really scary
Speaker 73: how many people in I don't know about the other states. I know Arizona, you know, we have a plethora of people they're endorsing and especially the one I'm running against, which is Hobbs or
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): Hobbs. Well, I'm running in tops. But Biggs is who they support here. And, you know, Biggs is.
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): is scary i mean to me i mean i try to help people understand
Speaker 73: like it bigs and hobs are both dangerous to arizona first off i've never i've lived in arizona my whole life i'm 41 years old and i've never seen arizona this bad and we are suffering as a state and suffering as providing i'm a provider healthcare providers are
Speaker 73: Health care is palmetting in our state. Homelessness is on the rise. These things are all connected. And if people think that Hobbs is
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): going to get us out of this, she helped put us in this. And Biggs, both of them have been in legislative office with a combined 50 years.
How
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): much longer? Angela has passed more laws and more bills into law than Biggs has. He has over a thousand sponsored bills and I can find one that's actually made it into law, which was just a name change of a Gilbert building. I mean, it's like it's incredibly what has he been doing for 30 years and now he wants to be governor. And I'm like, this is crazy.
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): unbelievable. And the things that continue to come out on
Speaker 73: him, you know, protecting his vote for no, that essentially
Speaker 25: protected convicted pedophiles eventually, Warren Jeff, you know, so all of these things that it's just really, really scary to think. And then just their allegiance to donors, special
interest,
and
Speaker 25: not the people and i try to say you know it both of them are just as dangerous it's a coin flip on who's worse for our state at this
Speaker 73: point so vote for me because and angela because we are not held back from all that stuff and we're we're going to make changes here in arizona that we need you know so stand up and do the right
Speaker 75: thing don't vote for the least of the worst vote for the person that the people that you know are actually going to do something in the state so
Speaker 76: the thing that i I found interesting, Teri, you just said,
and I just--
Speaker 76: grab my computer because
Speaker 67: it's so frustrating when you have someone who is supposed to be representing the citizens and the people of Arizona and they've been doing it for decades and multiple decades and they've submitted all these pieces of information all these bills into legislation and then nothing gets done and we've been paying their salary this
Speaker 77: entire time their entire job is to advocate for the citizens of Arizona
I did
Speaker 77: it for free, because it's the right thing to do. Now, of course, I was working full time someplace else.
But I
Speaker 77: was able to do this
Speaker 69: because every citizen out there has the right to do this. And they need to become more involved. And I, it's frustrating when I see people that get
Speaker 68: paid an exorbitant amount of money, and there's no results.
Yeah.
Speaker 78: Yeah, and to be to and, you know, as a health care provider today, and I'm sure there's lots of health care provide. I know a lot of health care providers are behind me in
Speaker 79 (higher-pitched voice): agencies. They don't speak out about it because we're retaliated against in our industry
Speaker 73: for for support and for supporting someone like me. But that we're supporting outwardly a person that is against, you know, or speaks against the government
Speaker 75: in such a way. And
Speaker 79 (higher-pitched voice): I say to people, I'm not against government. I'm against bad government. Right. And it's
not
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): government. It's the people in government that is being quarantined.
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): poorly driven, right? And, you know, Andy Biggs is one
Speaker 79 (higher-pitched voice): who's been, he's part of committees now and reform of agencies. And part of his agenda as a governor is to reform agencies. I'm like, you're
Speaker 80: literally part of that. He is part of the committee for, that he
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): won't recuse himself from so that the Epstein files can be investigated in Arizona. Well, Sasha Riley has named Andy Biggs as
part of
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): that so he's you know supposedly according to sasha riley and reports that and andy biggs hasn't denied that he also voted no for the epstein files to be released the first time then we know the second time he's voted yes but now we know they're all redacted most of them right so now
Speaker 79 (higher-pitched voice): there's a second go to get them released again and andy biggs according to ryan who just recently posted on this
Speaker 79 (higher-pitched voice): is not voting yes. So here he is speaking out and saying, I'm for children and all these things and showing videos of him
Speaker 73: and his grandkids. And I'm like, that's even more disgusting because you're not protecting kids, but yet you're a grandpa. Like,
Speaker 79 (higher-pitched voice): how can you be a grandpa with kids and then not protect kids on the other end? I just think it's...
Speaker 79 (higher-pitched voice): The fact is, is those are facts. He voted no
Speaker 81: on these bills that would have, these laws that would have helped children, right? And in addition,
Speaker 82: roll areas.
- Oh, I'll take it from here. No, I
Speaker 84: don't
Speaker 86 (higher-pitched voice): know if it's my stream that keeps going in and out, but maybe is it just mine or is it your guys's
too?
just
Speaker 87: you oh
Speaker 86 (higher-pitched voice): it's just mine because mine
Speaker 88: goes out mine goes out and then it like okay so it's mine okay that's good because
your wi-fi
Speaker 89: might not be
Speaker 90: that great
Speaker 89: yeah flame cocks um
real quick
Speaker 27: back um back to what angela said and then i'll tie it in
Speaker 92: you're right i'm really glad you made a distinction between TPUSA and Turning
Point
Speaker 92: action is the political arm.
Speaker 27: That is the 501c4. So TPUSA is the face of it. Everyone who's in tune with the Tyler Robinson case and Erica and what's going on, that's TPUSA. People forget about the 501c4. And you will also see that they're using a lot from Turning Point PAC. I've noticed this year they're using a lot. I look at like their golden ticket,
right?
Speaker 27: it's or their flyers and it'll say turning
Speaker 93: point pack um isn't there two more categories colin it's turning point action turning point usa
Speaker 94: turning point pack and then i think there's like there's an endowment and then there's also turning point america i believe and that's the only one
Speaker 95: that's based in indiana
i think
Speaker 95: yeah so they have a lot of so
Speaker 96: faith turning point faith also turning
Speaker 97: point usa faith
What
Speaker 4: is that? I'm not, I'm not familiar with Turning Point USA Faith.
Speaker 97: That is, that is just
Speaker 4: that? Yes. Okay.
So
Speaker 97: Turning
Speaker 93: Point USA Faith is, it's, that's how they're getting into the churches. Yeah, and it's,
Speaker 98: that's crazy.
Speaker 99: C4, C3. We're talking Harvest
Speaker 100: Church, Calvary is a big one, Dream City. So they're, they've gotten
Speaker 101: into the churches. By the way.
Speaker 102: Absolutely. And by the way, the
Speaker 1: churches that they are partnering with, in particular, like Greg Laurie, his
Speaker 103: church. Greg Laurie is the Dream City Church, isn't it? What church is Greg Laurie's? Was
Speaker 104: he Harvest? Is that the one with eight lawsuits? Harvest.
I
Speaker 103: think
Speaker 1: it's Harvest. Yeah, exactly. Harvest. I think it's Harvest. I'll just say Greg Laurie because I don't want to say the wrong church.
Speaker 105: I'll look
it up.
Okay,
Speaker 1: yeah, but I know Greg Laurie, the church that he runs, is particularly being under eight lawsuits for child S-trafficking from
Speaker 106: Romania. It is harvest. It is harvest,
Speaker 109: absolutely. It's a
lot
Speaker 108: of sexual offenses. I think all eight of them are sexual offenses.
Yeah.
I don't
Speaker 110: know if you paid
Speaker 111: attention to Candace, but one of the key threads that she keeps pulling on is all these people involved with Turning Point Faith and around Erica
Speaker 1: Kirk and also in Turning Point seem to all be connected to these child trafficking organizations. They either have non-profits of their own where they claim to be helping save victims or whatever, or they actually have children.
Speaker 1: charges you know being accused of doing it themselves looks
like
Speaker 112: this one's in the california this one's the california one the one that he's involved with is the california
Speaker 113: one
gotcha so
Speaker 114: there's harvest
Speaker 113: riverside here and that one wait hold on no that
is not the harvest church in
Speaker 113: glendale so it's in cal the one that i'm finding that he's a part of is not the one in arizona so i'll make that
Speaker 115: it's not the harvest church assemblies it's
the
it's
Speaker 115: a harvest church in california it's called harvest riverside it's his
Speaker 116: okay and i
Speaker 31: know in arizona they work with the harvest churches and calvary and especially dream city i know dream city
for
Speaker 77: sure dream city and i'm just doing a little research on my own here so turning point faith is actually a subsidiary program of turning point
usa
It's
Speaker 77: not a separate entity. It's the 501 C three. So underneath their educational. Got it.
So
Speaker 108: this is the way I look at it. Turning point faith is obviously infiltrating. I don't know if I should say
Speaker 117: that word, infiltrating the churches that's in the church. That's a good word.
Speaker 100: Okay. Yeah. Okay. Turning point faith is infiltrating the churches. TPUSA
Speaker 27: infiltrates the schools. That includes colleges and high schools. Now, as we recently heard,
is
Speaker 27: it Club America they held an assembly in a school so the students had no choice but to listen they their parents couldn't be there their
Speaker 92: parents had to sign off on it um there were some parents that kind of refused because
Speaker 27: you know and Charlie and Candace built the organization you don't force people you just you have a table on campus or you hold an event that's
Speaker 118: optional
right
Speaker 119: So
Speaker 118: now, with Club America, they're forcing assemblies in schools, and that was a high school. And middle
Speaker 120: school. It was a Christian school, a private
Speaker 1: Christian school, which is middle and high school both together, and they forced these students to go to an assembly where they had to be there, and if they didn't, then they were told that they were given an absence
Speaker 111: for that day, an unexcused absence.
Yeah.
I read
Speaker 122: that. I read that. Yeah. And, and just for like the, the viewers to know it
Speaker 123: too, is I, I'm a Christian, but I do believe in, you know, separation church and state. I don't want my church involved in my politics essentially. Right. And I think that not only protect and honestly churches are I go to CCB and they're the same way, right. They don't want to be involved in, in politics either. So it's very odd to me that churches such as dream city, that's an on them.
Speaker 123: according, I believe a non-denominational church, the, that would, they, they get involved.
And I
Speaker 123: think one of the things that is confusing about TPSA being in the Christian churches for a Christian myself or in Christian schools is that I think that they're widely confused by their own religious standpoint and, and religious viewpoints in terms of what, what are they teaching our children? So yeah,
You
Speaker 123: know, regardless of religious faith or not, I
Speaker 113: think that, you know, whatever religion, whatever group is, you know, again, whatever religion it is, whatever type of school it is, whether it's Christian or another LDS or any other type of religion in our that has a school and, you know, component, if there is any industry going in as a parent, if my kid was there.
Speaker 113: and let's
Speaker 123: just say, you know, whatever it is, let's just not even say it's Christian, let's just say it's LDS or
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): Catholic, or I would want the group to be the same faith, right? I mean, right, 'cause otherwise, I mean, what is, that's one of the first things I talk, I spoke out about that a while back, but I was like,
Speaker 113: this is so confusing because if I'm a parent and I'm taking my child to a faith focused school,
there
Speaker 113: are specific doctrines that that school is teaching my child right i mean that's what i would think as a parent and it's not just a hodgepodge of religion right and again not saying anything negative about religion any religion but just i would want those
Speaker 123: people to to be clear and to be aligned with the doctrine of whatever that church or whatever that school is and that's just what i find uh
Speaker 123: interesting because they're not they're not one type they're not focused on any type of religion
or
Speaker 31: aspect I don't think no
and once
Speaker 27: again I'm really glad you're bringing this up it's like you know they're a turning point overlooks due process
Speaker 124: and innocent to prove and guilty
and
Speaker 124: They're also overlooking the issues that are happening in these churches like SA allegations, SA charges, the R word, any of it.
Speaker 27: So, you know, the fact that Turning Point's willing to work with these churches that have, you know, that they're willing to be affiliated, you know, Turning Point has their own set of charges and allegations
to them.
Speaker 27: too. So maybe that's something they bond on. But no, it's really great to hear. I
Speaker 11: mean, you know, birds of a feather, right? So like I said, Turning Point Faith infiltrates the churches, USA infiltrates schools,
Speaker 59: and Turning Point Action infiltrates Arizona politics. I
just want to
Speaker 110: say one more thing as well. Particularly the churches that
Speaker 1: Turning Point gets involved with, I've noticed,
Speaker 1: That they are the evangelical churches, which basically have all been hijacked by Zionists who have been bastardizing the Bible
Speaker 6: to support their particular view on Israel. And that's another thing that bothers me, because they're corrupting the mind. They're using the Bible, corrupting the minds of our children to fit their specific narrative.
Speaker 123: Sure. Yeah. Yeah. And that's that should be questions if a parent has their child in a school where Turning Point USA is, I would say
Speaker 14: recommend to them to ask questions. Right. What are they teaching my child? Those are the questions that I would be asking
Speaker 125: if my child was in a in a private religious, whatever religion that is that people
Speaker 68: and our youth are just the absolute most influential.
Speaker 68: They are on so many levels and whether
Speaker 77: they are an audience or were an audience of Charlie Kirk, I'll never forget. I mean, the day that he was killed, my son at the time, who was 19, our youngest, picked up the phone, called me immediately and said, Mom, do not, do not,
Speaker 68: do not watch this. This just happened. Charlie Kirk was shot.
This
Speaker 68: just happened. Our youth,
they are
Speaker 68: getting in there, they're talking to them, they're preaching, no matter which angle you want to take, they're the most influential. And in Arizona, we have a massive, massive deficit here in education, we really need to fix our educational system, our schools here in Arizona, we are, we're not proud. I mean, at the very bottom of the barrel. I mean, it's really, really
Speaker 127: sad. And we have a lot of work to do here. A lot.
Speaker 128: Yeah, Terry,
Speaker 27: I heard in that clip interview, you know, he kept pressing you. Are you a Republican? Are you a Democrat? I like how you answered and said, I am a conservative because there's a distinctive difference that
Speaker 33: people don't understand.
Speaker 129: Yeah.
And
Speaker 129: unfortunately, a lot of the conservatives that we're describing
Speaker 27: that attend these churches, you know, they put their blinders up. They don't want to look into allegations or charges that their church or lawsuits their church is facing. You know, they don't want to accept the fact that, you know, Turning Point. I don't know. Do you know who Victor Marx is? No,
Speaker 11: he's part of Turning Point USA Faith. He's an actual he's a mercenary, essentially. He's admitted he has killed people.
Speaker 27: And he's also participated in voodoo and ritualistic
Speaker 92: sacrificing. He refers to it in his past, but it's like the conservatives in the church just completely put their blinders up
Speaker 59: and they, they don't want to acknowledge it. They don't want, they're in complete denial. And,
Speaker 33: you know, maybe segue a little bit into MAGA, you know, I was going to tell you that,
Speaker 33: - He's
Speaker 130: running for Colorado governor, by the way.
- What? - Victor Marx
Speaker 130: is running for Colorado governor, by the way.
-
Speaker 93: Oh, wow. - Yeah, and he has turning point backing. So there's another convenience. But no,
Speaker 27: I was gonna tell you these,
you know,
Speaker 27: the conservatives, a lot of them in the churches have their head buried in the sand. I'm not trying to be mean, but they have their head buried in
the sand.
They
Speaker 27: don't want to talk about Israel unless it's the you know biblical and they're like no you know this is what we stand with. They don't want to acknowledge turning points flaws or all the line and the dishonest the dishonesty since Charlie has passed. So I was going to tell
you.
I
Speaker 27: don't know if I if I were you, I'd even waste my time with the MAGA, the people that are still diehard MAGA. You know, they're probably a lost cause. Andy Biggs is endorsed by Trump. So there goes that. My advice
Speaker 131: to you and I mean, are you canvassing? Do you all have door knockers?
Speaker 63 (higher-pitched voice): Yeah, so so.
Speaker 63 (higher-pitched voice): Yeah. It's me and Angela. And you know what we're going to do? We're still going to win because God's army
is bigger
Speaker 132: than the
Speaker 133: two above that attitude. I'm like, all right, God, you know, it is, you know, it's talking.
Speaker 56 (higher-pitched voice): I do podcasts. I've I'm blessed with you guys. I'm blessed with I'll be in. I'm actually
Speaker 79 (higher-pitched voice): headed out to Havasu today. Mojave County, Kingman. I'm on the radio tomorrow for
Speaker 73: with, you know,
I'll
Speaker 73: put it on my site but it's in Havasu radio and then I'm with a pilots group on Saturday speaking to a pilots group
and
Speaker 134: then Friday Kingman if anybody's in Kingman with the you know the first Friday of Kingman yeah so the
you
Speaker 133: know
Speaker 56 (higher-pitched voice): just doing I talk a lot do a lot of social media.
Speaker 56 (higher-pitched voice): You know, I walk around,
Speaker 79 (higher-pitched voice): you know, some of the some of the tricks of the play that are, you know, my my my secret, my secret. I will share after I
Speaker 135: win, but I haven't shared my secret yet, how I won that primary fully. It worked the first time. Yeah.
Speaker 137: And it's all
Speaker 136: working. It's
Speaker 137: all it's all honest and no back doors. And and, you know, it really is
Speaker 79 (higher-pitched voice): grit. So my saying is.
uh
Speaker 79 (higher-pitched voice): people can look this up i even set it on the one the clip that you shared too and i said you know this is uh how'd you do it and i said well it's about people right and a whole lot of jesus and grit and you know people are like no really how'd you do it i'm like no that's really how i did it people and a whole lot of jesus and grit okay it's work it's a you know i'm putting
Speaker 18: 110 in i you know work hard and people need to know that i i do work too i'm a therapist right i still am a
And
Speaker 18: and and so, you know, and Angela works, too. And it's we we are people
Speaker 135: that are not bought. We are not bought. And that is so important
Speaker 73: that people really grasp that concept of not being bought,
Speaker 25: because that if you think for one minute that any any candidate or politician in our state or nation who has tremendous endorsements or donors or PACs influencing their policy, It's just they answer
to
Speaker 25: to them first and foremost. And Andy Biggs has voted no many times for protecting children. I mean, it's like, how can Turning Point get behind this POS? But honestly--
Speaker 139: - Money, that's why.
Speaker 139: Like I said, it's a way to play, that's how they operate.
Speaker 141 (higher-pitched voice): Yeah. And so, you know, and I, and I think when you said like the, the MAGA or the lost cause, I can understand you saying
Speaker 142 (higher-pitched voice): that. I'd say, I'd say still even try with them though too. Like I look at everyone as like, like, um, you know, and I, when they say like, I'm for, you know, for Trump and all these things. And I'm not, I say to people,
Speaker 138: listen,
Speaker 138: I'm going to work with Trump. I bet Trump will love me. OK. And because I have a you're
Speaker 144: a good looking woman.
Speaker 138: Trump loves women,
you know, good
Speaker 144: looking women.
Speaker 145: But, you know, I'm not going to be as beck and call.
Speaker 142 (higher-pitched voice): Right. And he takes us that guess to everything and know to if it helps Arizonans. But.
uh
Speaker 142 (higher-pitched voice): the fact is that listen the it's about people even trump is supposed to be for the people first right and so is andy biggs and so is every other elected officials it's not supposed to be president first we elite to alleged president first right that's not here in america and therefore we shouldn't want that in america and so i do have good conversations with people who are quote maga and i think i have i i've
Speaker 142 (higher-pitched voice): i've i've flipped many of them over to me because i think they're
Speaker 146: just you know a lot of people feel betrayed a lot they
Speaker 59: do absolutely they feel betrayed they felt like they were lied to and i feel like a lot of them feel unmotivated they do not want to get out and vote and that's
Speaker 27: another population i wanted to run by you um
I
Speaker 27: think, you know, that's what Turning Point does, you know, get boots on the ground. They're known for door knocking. They're known for canvassing, but they're also known for targeting low propensity voters, Republican, low propensity voters. So people that forgot, you know, that weren't involved, didn't vote in the last midterms. We need to get those people.
Speaker 33: Yeah. Because they're feeling very unmotivated right now. I think they're disillusioned. I think they're discouraged. A lot of people were discouraged by the current administration. So I would definitely encourage you to go after the Republican low propensity voters. Most of the Democrats are set in stone with Katie Hobbs. Most of them are just, you know. Yeah. I
Speaker 149: flipped a
Speaker 56 (higher-pitched voice): lot of them, too.
No, really. Yeah. Yeah. So, you know, part of my story is, you know, what I like to say.
Speaker 56 (higher-pitched voice): say is i voted for
Speaker 79 (higher-pitched voice): katie hobbs and and you know and that's part of my statement to people is like listen i know we believe the lies we drink the kool-aid so did i i drank the kool-aid of you're gonna she's gonna send a support business and i will tell
you that
Speaker 79 (higher-pitched voice): i'd say it all the time is if katie hobbs would have picked up my phone call in 2024 i may not be here
Speaker 73: today but watching my company demolished like thousands of other providers in the state of arizona today you know businesses has been open for decades in arizona serving the public and this woman could care less
Speaker 73: It's her state agency. It's like, it's
Speaker 123: her fault. It's Andy Biggs fault. It's the representative's
Speaker 79 (higher-pitched voice): fault. It's not the federal government's fault. The way I look at it is, if the federal government we fight, we can fight back, we can argue, we can disagree, whatever. But at the end of the
day, as
Speaker 79 (higher-pitched voice): governor, if I am elected there, and Angela,
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): we, we will, uh,
Of
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): course, not say everything's great that like Andy Bitt federal government will push back if we need to. But if they make the call of something, then we're going to say, OK, this is what we have. And as we're CEOs, we've done that. Right. We're entrepreneurs. Right. We have that mindset of, OK, this is what I have. What what can I do with it now? How do I arrange this?
Right.
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): legally, ethically, honestly, and make this right for Arizona. Not say, oh, the federal government, I can't do anything, my hands are tied. The governor has so much power
Speaker 123: to help the people today. And people need to understand that there's 130 agencies underneath the governor in Arizona. And I'll tell you that if we say one minute that the SNAP benefits that are being paid out to our people isn't her fault,
Speaker 123: you're i'm sorry but it is her fault okay and as governor i would step into that agency immediately and and what i'm going to do is reform and you know come in and flip some tables because what's happening in arizona are people are being harmed by the highest people that are in these
Speaker 73: positions and they're they're going to lose their jobs and many of them know it when i'm if i'm elected that they're going to lose their jobs
Speaker 73: uh, because I'm tired of people
Speaker 123: hurting people. You are a government employee. You are subject to the people and you are hurting people. And, you know, it's, it is when Angela said she ran for office, you know, to, that really is, it's like, okay, what can I do to help
Speaker 150: people? Cause no one's listening. Oh, I'll
run for governor. And
Speaker 150: then I want, I'm
Speaker 21: like, oh, I'm still, I can't
Speaker 151: believe it. I mean,
Speaker 150: I don't think you can argue.
Speaker 152: I mean, you're very proactive. Even in your first statements,
I'm like,
Speaker 152: You know, lawsuits calling
Speaker 27: Katie Hobbs firsthand, like you're obviously proactive, which is great. That's what we need. And, you know, a lot of them are they act like
Speaker 118: they're blameless. You know, my hands are tied. You hit the nail on the head.
Speaker 153: Yeah. And honestly.
Speaker 4: plans that take 15 years to implement and they won't even be in the office at that point in time so yeah and
Speaker 155: that's what they're banking on that's what they're banking on they're like oh we'll start it but i'm not going to
finish it yeah
Speaker 156: um but i do have and
Speaker 157: that's one of the that's one
Speaker 110: of the things that bothers
Speaker 1: me about katie hobbs
too is
Speaker 1: you know she she actually had there's
many of us
Speaker 1: that would have gotten behind her had she would have
You
Speaker 1: know, gone after Turning Point and gone after the corruption because people there are so many people
Speaker 6: that have been, you know, trying to get her to go after the corruption within Turning Point for many, many years. And she just refuses to do it. I
Speaker 5: don't know whether it's because she's just scared or whether because they have blackmail on her or something. I don't know. But for whatever reason, she seems to her inaction, like you said,
Speaker 6: her inaction is what. Yeah.
Speaker 6: She's
Speaker 123: scared. She's paid off. She's bought. All these things are true. I mean, about her. You know, I mean, I mean, it's
Speaker 73: my opinion. She's scared. It's the truth.
And
Speaker 77: the other hard part is, I mean, she's literally known as the veto governor. And instead of a whole different
Speaker 4: perspective, how do we get to yes?
If
Speaker 4: they are things that are of value, why do we just say no, no, no? I mean, that doesn't work. She even
Speaker 159: vetoed like the Charlie Kirk highway or something. I mean, you're right. She vetoes everything. Yeah,
she vetoes
Speaker 160: everything. Right. And and she stands
Speaker 79 (higher-pitched voice): behind that, too. She doesn't you know, and now she wants to say to people.
Speaker 79 (higher-pitched voice): oh, I'm bipartisan. I'm across the line. I'm like, lady, you cannot come back and say you're across the line. I mean, Andy Biggs is doing it too. He voted no on protections of equality in Arizona and different parts of it. And yet he's, you know, now they're both trying to be this, it's just, it's really
Speaker 73: infuriating. And it should be to a lot of people when you see
At
Speaker 73: least for me, it is too, especially being internal to this process now, you see just the complete and utter lie to the public from public officials. It's why people hate government. I
Speaker 161: mean, because they just get away with lying.
And then
Speaker 161: the other part is, you
Speaker 77: know, in this race, for example, you have our current governor and lieutenant candidate.
they
Speaker 77: won't debate they won't engage they won't be part of the system they won't so unfortunately because of that you know events that would typically happen throughout the state they have to cancel other events now because we can't even get the
Speaker 162: democratic you know participants to be to
show up to
Speaker 162: show up they won't even show up and that's really sad so
Speaker 163: you're saying that that they're
Speaker 164: scared to even
Speaker 162: debate you they
Speaker 164: won't debate
wow wow
-
Speaker 162: That's correct. And even,
Speaker 77: you know, there was a recent event where it was simply Biggs and Hobbs.
Speaker 165: And even though they both showed up at the same event, they weren't even allowed to be on the stage at the same time or in the building at the same time because she was not willing to engage in any kind of cross
Speaker 67: communication, so to speak. - Yeah. -
Speaker 166: It's unfortunate. So when the debates happen here next week, they are not participating.
Speaker 86 (higher-pitched voice): - Yeah, so 10:05, Monday at 6:00 PM, Angela debates
Speaker 86 (higher-pitched voice): signed
Speaker 73: care which is the lieutenant governor with andy biggs and then on 10-6 i debate biggs uh and the green candidate who may or may not show up because she is likely may have some fraud indictments
Speaker 125: here coming on her way no
joke
Speaker 167: that's true actually
Speaker 168: this
Speaker 169: stuff up it just happened you
Speaker 168: can't make it
up
Speaker 169: That's great. I
Speaker 170 (higher-pitched voice): do have to ask because you are a native to Arizona. We
Speaker 93: are in the state of Arizona. One of the big crises that we've had is the border issue. And
Speaker 131: Katie Hobbs wasn't compliant in the beginning. I haven't heard much on that since. I haven't seen Tom Holman in a while. I don't even know where he is. But how do you feel about that?
How
Speaker 131: do you feel about ICE and Homeland Security?
Speaker 78: Yeah, so, and I don't know. Colin, do you know your
Speaker 63 (higher-pitched voice): camera's off or did you? Yeah. Oh, okay, perfect.
Speaker 78: Okay, I didn't know.
Speaker 171: Okay, no
Speaker 63 (higher-pitched voice): worries. I didn't know.
Speaker 78: Let's have a
Speaker 171: wait for a second. It's
Speaker 78: okay. I didn't know. You know, if my camera goes out, you guys tell me. Yeah, I've been having issues. But I
Speaker 79 (higher-pitched voice): support ICE in law enforcement. We support ICE in law enforcement. We don't support violence. We support free speech. We don't support violent protests. We support protests. So
very cool.
Speaker 79 (higher-pitched voice): common sense right um people shouldn't be harmed and tortured uh and or detention centers oh
oh you're frozen i
Speaker 125: don't know if i can still be heard but okay it's just my screen is acting funny all right i don't know what's
Speaker 172: going on i don't know what the
Speaker 79 (higher-pitched voice): heck uh maybe it's tyler boyer just messing with us right here it
Speaker 173: might be
I'm
Speaker 173: sure he's watching.
Speaker 176 (higher-pitched voice): Yeah. So anyways, we support law enforcement. We don't support violence. I don't support
Speaker 79 (higher-pitched voice): immunity, neither does Angela, immunity against cops and those things. But if they do a crime, they should do the time. But
Speaker 177 (higher-pitched voice): again, as a common sense area of people
Speaker 177 (higher-pitched voice): I say to
Speaker 79 (higher-pitched voice): people all the time, it's like, so it's one of the main questions I get in the community. Do you support ICE? And I answer just like that. And I say, if you don't support law enforcement in federal government, then what gives you the right to call the police, right? What gives you the right to call 911 when you need them, right? And so do they commit crime? Absolutely. And they should be prosecuted for the crimes, but they also save
a lot
Speaker 79 (higher-pitched voice): of
Speaker 73: lives.
Speaker 73: that are needed in our communities, our state, our nation. And so I hope that's the real round. And I think a lot of people don't realize-- there's been immigration practices in the United States for a century. And ICE has been around since 2003 and post 9/11. And so it's just recently that there's all this storm about ICE and it's coming in the news.
And
Speaker 73: should there be some reform or those things? I mean, sure. I mean, I think there's reform available
Speaker 125: in all systems. Right. And ensure that ultimately people are not being harmed in our state.
Speaker 59: I like your I like your mentality, you know, your pro law enforcement enforcing the law. If someone has broken a law, you
Speaker 93: know, they have to.
Speaker 93: do the crime, pay the time, and you know, because we are,
Speaker 27: you know, a big state when it comes to this, you know, we're by California, New Mexico, so, and I know Katie Hobbs was not very compliant, and there's been a lot of, you know, legislators and other public officials that have been very rebellious, and you know,
and I'm
I'm
Speaker 27: not trying to be like racist, but, you know, you know, a lot of them are Hispanic legislators and public officials and they have made X. They've gone on X. They've gone on social media and they've warned people. They've started, you know, ISIS come into this area, you
Speaker 33: know, ISIS come into this neighborhood and then they
get people
Speaker 33: riled up and then they get violent
Speaker 178: towards the law enforcement that comes. Yeah. And honestly, even worse than that, they've
been.
Speaker 179: They've been doxing ICE agents too. They even made websites doxing ICE agents.
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): Well, it's really, you know, it's come to a point. I mean, can you imagine just being, having
Speaker 123: that amount of protest that really is, it becomes
Speaker 18: harmful to the public, right? When they're jumping in front of cars, when they're honking horns, blow horns and all these things that we see.
Speaker 18: And, you know, in
Speaker 79 (higher-pitched voice): Arizona, you know, one of
the things
Speaker 79 (higher-pitched voice): that I believe it was Tucson, I don't have to look this up, but I believe it was Tucson, I can look it up now, but that made a law that passed, I believe it passed, where they can't come in without a warrant, they can't even stay anywhere without a warrant
anymore.
Speaker 79 (higher-pitched voice): I believe it was Pima County, that, that won't be statewide, you know, for us, it's like the federal government needs to be safe in the ability to
Speaker 57: be, they should have a warrant, right, but they should be able to ask questions to just follow the law,
Speaker 181 (higher-pitched voice): right? I mean, can we all just follow the law? You know, honestly.
Speaker 181 (higher-pitched voice): Again, I'm all for protest, right? I'm all for it. I love protests. I don't do it personally, but I love it.
Speaker 57: I love free speech. I don't want to quiet that down, right? If we don't have that, it's not American, I don't think. But ultimately, let's not
put
Speaker 115: ourselves in danger or other people in danger just
Speaker 23: to protest,
right?
I
Speaker 115: mean,
Speaker 77: you asked originally about just border security in general, and you know, everybody wants to talk about ICE and ICE's job is absolutely to basically remove people who are subject to any type of federal immigration enforcement. So you've got ICE and then separately, you've got CBP, you've
Speaker 68: got Border Patrol. They're the ones that are federal, they are working down on the border. That is their job.
Speaker 68: They are trying to prevent unlawful entry. But unfortunately,
Speaker 183 (higher-pitched voice): they end up helping those that have crossed and moving them into facilities to either get care or treatment or be returned or unite families. We have gotten away from what the actual enforcement initiatives are.
you
Speaker 183 (higher-pitched voice): know, at least on that federal side. And then if you look at actual border security and you're looking at Arizona, you know, Arizona's job specifically is to make sure that we are protecting our citizens of Arizona. And that goes beyond ICE, that goes beyond CBP and Border Patrol, that goes down to our state, to our county sheriffs, it goes to Arizona DPS here. And they're focusing on making sure they're reducing fentanyl, that they're preventing human smuggling. So the issues are so layered,
Speaker 183 (higher-pitched voice): And you've got federal issues layered with state issues, layered with local enforcement opportunities. So I think that as a society, we have gotten so distracted by protesting things that may not even relate to what's happening, but everybody wants to be heard.
And I
Speaker 183 (higher-pitched voice): get that. Everyone should be heard. But back to your original point, everyone just follow
the law,
Speaker 183 (higher-pitched voice): follow the process, go
Speaker 184: through it, you know, and we'll make sure you're taken care of, however that's supposed to
be.
I
Speaker 185: think absolutely.
Speaker 54: I actually, you know, I think a lot of the protests stem not necessarily from the immigration itself, the enforcement of
Speaker 1: the immigration. I think it's more their tactics and how they go about it.
Speaker 1: You know, because like I agree, I'm 100 percent in agreement with we need to enforce our our borders, enforce our immigration laws. You know, if you're here illegally, that is a crime. You know, a lot of people don't like to admit that. It is a crime. OK. But.
The
Speaker 1: way they go about it, you know, violently against some of these people by going after, you know, Trump had promised in part of his campaigning that they were going to go after the the violent criminals, the gang members and stuff first. And instead, to meet their quotas, what they were doing was they were going after just, you know, just Joe Blow, the guys that were just had a family and were, you know, working on the corner.
you
Speaker 1: know, trying to earn a living to feed their family. Yeah. And then they were going to the, even worse, they were going to the court hearings where these people were lawfully
Speaker 189: showing up for their hearings and arresting them before they could even go into the hearing. Yes.
Speaker 79 (higher-pitched voice): Trapping people is not okay. So that is not okay. I want to make, so in Arizona, I, we're for legal immigration
Speaker 190: and totally with you on that, but we need, we do need, you know,
Speaker 123: resources and a pathway for people that have been here for, you know, our, - Yeah.
Speaker 123: system has largely
Speaker 73: failed, right? And it failed people. And I think ripping families apart today for when we can provide resources, we can have a pathway to citizenship. Many of them are already on that pathway of citizenship, and then they're pulled, right?
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): And again, with the idea, with the understanding, which I do, it is against the law to be here legally, right? But trapping people and doing all
these
Speaker 57: things.
Speaker 57: should not be what we what
we do
Speaker 57: in America. Right. So I come from the
Speaker 66: State Department of all places, the U.S. Department of State.
Speaker 183 (higher-pitched voice): And our job is basically to help facilitate and give permission through the visa process for individuals to legally and successfully get here to the United States, give them permission. And these people try really hard. They try incredibly hard for the lineage, their entire family. They might wait decades. You know, Vietnam people have been waiting 30 years to come over here.
Speaker 183 (higher-pitched voice): And, you know, I totally support ICE. I support them carrying out lawful immigration enforcement. It's simple. But I also think that they should absolutely prioritize, prioritize violent offenders, traffickers. I mean, everybody, people who are actually committing crimes, not those that are working twice as hard as you and I.
to
Speaker 183 (higher-pitched voice): do jobs you and I don't even want to do. So they're working harder, they're working faster, they're working twice as much. And but again, legally, they need to follow the process. We want we are an amalgamation. This nation that we live in is the most beautiful nation in the world. We have people from everywhere here. And it is truly, it is a beautiful freedom.
and
Speaker 183 (higher-pitched voice): they sometimes appreciate it more than we do especially those that have waited decades to get here who have have petitioned for their entire families to come over these aren't the same people that are committing serious violent crimes and or have other malintentions when they come to the united states whether they're coming through our border here in arizona or whatever the case is so i really just think that it's you know we need to
We
Speaker 183 (higher-pitched voice): need to respect our local law enforcement, our state law enforcement, our federal law enforcement, but they need to operate absolutely within the Constitution and respect due process back to your due process. I think that that's what it's about. I mean, there is a system, there is a process. And if we're all doing it the right way, then there shouldn't be all of this upheaval.
And
Speaker 191: Angela's bilingual, by the way, too, Spanish. Oh,
Speaker 192: that's awesome.
Speaker 194: No
Speaker 193: coming handy here. I'm Mexican and I don't even speak it. I'm Norwegian. I speak
a
Speaker 195: little bit of it.
Un
Speaker 196: poquito. I know that. No. Con a new y la cerveza.
Speaker 131: Yeah, that's great. And I agree with you. You
Speaker 59: know, that Charlie Kirk said that, you know, just do it right. Don't cut in front of people, the people that are desperately trying to do things the right way and they're waiting in line. Don't, you know, don't
cut in
Speaker 198: front of people. So
Speaker 69: and I've said this to Terry, I've said other platforms before, and it's oversimplifying the process. But, you know, I welcome
Speaker 77: people from all different countries. But if you come to my home in the middle of the night and you
Speaker 68: want to come in my house, Yes.
You
Speaker 68: better knock on the door and ask for permission because if you come in through a window, you have a problem, right? You're not going to be near as welcome. I'm going to probably throw you out the other window. But if you come in and you ask for permission to come to my house, whether no matter what day it is, what time it is, and you knock and you agree
to
Speaker 183 (higher-pitched voice): help out while you're here and do your part, there's a good chance I'm going to let you in. Yeah.
Yeah.
Yeah. And
Speaker 199: people are
Speaker 200: armed. People in Arizona are armed. Right. So you put the door, not the window. Are you pro-gun? You're in Arizona.
Speaker 201: Yes. Oh, yeah. We're pro-gun. I
got
Speaker 202: one on me just now. Just kidding.
Speaker 202: There, I have a couple more important,
Speaker 203: well, I have a couple more important questions.
Speaker 204: Angela, if you have to go, I don't know. I have a few
Speaker 205: minutes
Speaker 203: more
Speaker 11: of it.
Speaker 205: Okay. Okay. All right. I didn't want to say, oh, don't go yet. No, I'm still here though. Yeah, I'm still here.
Okay. Well,
Speaker 92: obviously this is a...
Speaker 92: national problem, this is a global problem, but you know, Phoenix is one of the top cities for human trafficking.
Speaker 131: And as a matter of fact, we're headquartered, we're turning point headquarters is, um, on that Tempe Phoenix line is one of the worst sites for human trafficking. So I was wondering, did you have any thoughts on combating that? Um, are you familiar with Jerry Sheridan? I'm, are you? Yes.
Speaker 122: Okay.
Do you
Speaker 122: want to
speak on it? Yeah.
Well, I
Speaker 208: just think, I mean, human trafficking as a whole and how we're addressing it in
Speaker 77: Arizona, I think it's a huge challenge and actually one of the biggest draws for human smuggling trafficking and trafficking of minors and us trafficking, all of those kind of things. The draws are tied to large scale events oftentimes. Yeah.
Speaker 209: There was
a
Speaker 77: massive interdiction or teams that were put together as a part of the Super Bowl, maybe the Super Bowl. Yeah, Super Bowl is one
Speaker 210: of the biggest ones.
Speaker 77: yeah so i think arizona because we have big big events that are a big draw it creates this focal point you know for arizona and of course our access to the border it's a big issue and again this is kind of tied this gets tied back ultimately to you know border patrol and ice and all those things but then how do you get beyond
Speaker 77: Again, these, this is the focus on the true violent offenders. This is the true orchestrators of the smuggling rings. Those are the ones that you want to get to. It's the one offs, two offs. I mean, yes, of course, we want to address everyone as an issue, but we're the ringleader. That's who you need to get. Sure.
And,
Speaker 33: you know, like you all mentioned, getting the low hanging fruit with illegals, the ones that are committing crime, the ones that are
Speaker 27: pushing drugs. You know, we've got to get the low hanging fruit because, you know, some of them are responsible for the human trafficking.
Speaker 211: I've worked
Speaker 27: a little bit with some organizations that are trying to fight, you know, and combat human trafficking.
Speaker 27: they said these operations are intense. They're sophisticated. If, you know, if, if these underground operations, if they even get wind that somebody's caught on to them, they just pick up and uproot and move.
I
Speaker 77: mean, they're very hard. Their entire operation, their entire operation. And I know that, for example, like you mentioned Sheridan. So he's the MCSO sheriff right now. He's the designated sheriff. Yes. Yes. And great And he's been part of MCS
over and over.
Speaker 77: many, many years and served under a different reign. But obviously, that's a big focus here in Maricopa County on many different levels. But again, I don't think it's just the county enforcement or the county recognition or their task forces. I believe it actually just spans statewide. Yeah.
And I think that's
Speaker 78: one of the things when we think about the border
Speaker 123: security people, oftentimes, they want to say, we don't want a border wall because they're thinking
about
But we
Speaker 123: have to think about the smuggling, the trafficking, people being left in the desert every single year to die, families to die. And for us, we want border security. But, you know, a lot of people don't realize that in the border wall of Arizona, at least with a fact, there are certain parts of the border wall that there's holes in it, which is for migration, animals or certain watering holes. Lights are being used differently, those types of things that.
Speaker 123: And we're all for that, right? We shouldn't destroy tribal land. There's tribes that could be harmed if the law goes into certain areas and takes out where people are buried. And it was
Speaker 73: just sad to think about that. Some people,
Speaker 213: when I was
at
Speaker 73: an event recently,
And
Speaker 73: they talked about that. Right. They've talked about their family members being buried in certain parts and they're going to they may have to go engrave them and move them somewhere else. And we're talking about people, tribal people.
And I
Speaker 73: just feel like that's really kind of cruel. Right. There are things that we can do that we can put extra security up in certain areas. But my goodness, should we make people.
Speaker 214: bring up their their loved ones i don't know i don't think so so
yeah yeah that's that's just another big issue
Speaker 215: but i mean that's a global epidemic it's a national epidemic i think it's a global epidemic so i know
Speaker 4: that's going to be a one you know one
of the tying
Speaker 4: a little bit of this
Speaker 77: but talking about the border wall you know yes there's there's breaks in the wall it's basically open on either end but the reality is is
the
Speaker 77: struggles that are down on the border are multi-layered and what they're basically you have families that are going up to the wall and they're taking their family members who have a significant disease illness or injury and they're literally throwing them over the
wall and
Speaker 77: they're throwing them over the wall into the united states into arizona so that they can get help
Speaker 68: and they can get treatment and they can get support because as a citizen here well or non-citizen if you are brought to a hospital they will treat
you
And
Speaker 68: then one of the greatest challenges down there along the border is that there's no funding for these hospitals. They're going under, you know, the urgent cares can't sustain themselves because they're busy treating primarily illegal immigrants into the U.S. And that's a massive challenge, too. So, you know, the border issues, the wall issues span many different, many different categories. And like I said, it even goes into health care.
Speaker 55 (higher-pitched voice): Yeah, I want to. I just realized there's a comments over here that I can actually see.
So
Speaker 13: I want to apologize to people commenting. I'm sorry. Are you away with
Speaker 216: questions? Yeah, I'm
Speaker 13: perfectly fine. I love it. You know, if people reach out to me, I'm one of the very few people that actually comments, but I just found them. So sorry, everyone for not responding.
i
Speaker 13: didn't realize i could actually see these so i i will say um the one thing that uh thanks patty tauba uh voting for you ladies the debate it's actually a joke it's not a joke
Speaker 18: uh the debate tonight is bigs doing it on his own platform um it's really bizarre to be honest with you um it's uh the bigs debate is actually on tuesday at 10 6 with clean elections it'll be myself bigs and at 6 p.m i i think it's just him on his own stage it's
Speaker 18: very bizarre um so the
um she
Speaker 18: asked if I was part of it no he they want to pretend like I don't exist um but I do and so they'll see
and I
Speaker 57: guess be surprised like
the uh
Speaker 57: Hugh Lytle who I beat in the primary
who
Speaker 13: you know thought he didn't he
Speaker 217: didn't
show
Speaker 13: the debate and his team told me afterwards um
He just
Speaker 13: thought he had it in the bucket. And I'm like, well, I kicked his butt. I guess
Speaker 108: not. Well, you know, there's still of the mentality that third party vote is a wasted vote. You know, people say, yeah,
people
Speaker 218: say, Terry, you're not even on the you're so low on the polls. I'm like, I'm not even on
Speaker 19: the polls. I'm not even on the polls. I have I'm not on the polls. How could I even register on the polls and be anywhere on the polls? My name is not there. You know, I mean, so it's not fair to begin with. So, yeah.
Speaker 19: And then KK says, "Will Mays retry Bauer or Tyler?" And in Arizona, a governor can, there's laws in place that a governor can implement. And I don't know the word for it, and I'd have to look up the ARS, but to-
Speaker 219: - It was actually my next question.
Speaker 62: Like as far as his charges, he was pardoned by the president,
you
Speaker 62: know, how do you feel? How do you feel, you know, they were dropped? Do you think they should be dropped on a state level? No,
I
Speaker 57: mean, I think if people are charged, you know, I think that they should. And we just saw President Trump didn't step into the Lindsay Clancy thing, right? So he said it was a state thing. So, you know, I think state and again, I don't want to say Tyler is guilty, not guilty, all these things, right? We believe in due process. And certainly I'm going to say that for him too, but the thing is
that
Speaker 57: There has to be some due process here and investigation and what's happening. And I think he's you know, I think there's a huge problem. And we see that based on the words in finance. Right. And some of the things that have come out regarding that. And just all of the people that are talking about and showing a lot of evidence that you can't just close your eyes to. You've got to wonder what the heck is going on
here.
Speaker 57: and so it you know it's um it's really it's really interesting but again uh it the attorney general i think um you know mays i've widely i've talked against mays for some time but then um because she didn't do anything for providers in the state of arizona but now it's either her or
Speaker 57: warren peterson warren peterson is bought by turning point now he didn't accept the endorsement until july and so now i'm really not okay with that so it's like what could be who's worse you know and i i honestly think that anyone is who's endorsed by turning point is probably the worst that's my opinion
Speaker 220: that's how i speak
Speaker 13: oh 100 so uh i'm like okay i think um so my direction
Speaker 57: has
Speaker 57: You know, again, I'd want to see Mays do something. And I think we can, the governor has the opportunity to do investigations through state county attorneys and those things to, and address the AG into doing an investigation, which I would do. So, you know, again, due process.
Speaker 92: that's one of the things i really like about you thus far is that you're like no it's the law we're measuring this by the law and yeah you know it's like you you
Speaker 27: broke the law you have charges like we have to deal with that accordingly it's not who your uncle is or who you grew up with or
Speaker 221: who you go to church with or who's
Speaker 222: donating yeah it needs
Speaker 223: to be dealt with
Speaker 92: yeah
so yeah i appreciate that
Speaker 92: And I like your optimism about, you know, I think you should target low
Speaker 34: propensity voters. I think you should target independents. But it sounds like you're optimistic to all of them, which I think is great.
Speaker 224: You know, I have a video
Speaker 225: that started that I started. And again, it's my secret. It's called my secret to how I won.
I love
Speaker 226: it.
Speaker 228: like everywhere i travel
Speaker 226: yeah and i don't share it because
Speaker 56 (higher-pitched voice): you know people still wonder how did i win that primary and i'll tell you guys it's it's a people jesus grit okay it comes down to those that recipe those ingredients
Speaker 25: but it's nothing um you know it's nothing anybody couldn't do but um i won't share it until the end so what
i'm doing yeah we'll get
Speaker 229: your secret recipe later on i guess yeah there you go
Speaker 110: by the way i i think there's
uh
You
Speaker 110: said you're not in the polls yet or whatever, so it's
Speaker 1: kind of hard to judge where you stand or whatever. But
I think in
Speaker 1: particular, there is a big swath of people that were formerly in the MAGA movement that have now moved quietly into the independent
Speaker 230: category. You know, where they're in a silent majority.
Speaker 137: Yeah. Yeah. A lot of people don't know...
Speaker 18: A lot of people know I exist because of my social media, I'm not as big on x, x is hard to grow. But kudos to you guys. It's, you know, some of the other platforms I grew much faster on but, you know, it's, that's how I, you know, I'm recognized through the social media a lot of
Speaker 14: times and just I walk around and talk to people and those things but
it
Speaker 73: is really a grassroots, and it's a God story, right, it's a, it is, but we are, you know, for those who are Christian or,
Speaker 18: or religious or any, you know, whatever you, spiritual, whatever that is to
Speaker 14: you and your definition of, right, it's, it's, we don't get to just sit by on the sidelines and say, well, you know, it's taken care of, no, we work hard, and
Speaker 14: you put everything in as you can can, and, and we travel and we do, and it's mostly, you know, self-funded and some
Speaker 22: donations. And certainly if, uh, you know, prayer and donations are the things that help us the most. So it's
Speaker 63 (higher-pitched voice): like, and just good thoughts and a vote. Right. And a lot of people, I'm not, I'm not big on, you
Speaker 18: know, I rarely ask for, for anything, to be honest, I've probably put out five times in the entirety of my campaign ever asking for a donation, but,
um,
Speaker 18: Because ultimately people in Arizona are suffering and I get the text from Katie Hobbs team probably because I used to be a Democrat. But, you know, I mean, I'm getting like six in a week and I'm like, man, this lady is spending text messages for everyone to know. They cost a lot of money, anywhere from two cents to six cents per text.
So
Speaker 18: you imagine she's spending millions of dollars on text messages begging and she's lying and outward. I mean, I've shown it through my post. She lies on her text to people like she had one that came
Speaker 25: out that she was one point away on the polls from Biggs. And oh, my gosh, hurry up and give to us. And I'm like, no, you're not. You're according to the polls. You're like 12 points ahead of Biggs. So why would you tell people? And that's just it's just
so.
Speaker 25: heartbreak you know as much as i hate i don't hate her i dislike her very much katie hobbs um but i still don't want to see people harmed in our state regardless of party i don't like people being lied to um i don't think that that's needed i've always said that's not needed you don't need millions of dollars to win this um you need to it's about people and i think what people will
in
Speaker 25: the debate stage too is that we are people we're you know we're people not politicians and we speak from our heart and uh connect with the heart because we know what's happening um i've struggled and i've i've experienced success right too in my life so it's um and as as most people have in some level
Speaker 232: adversity can be a gift. Yeah. There's no question about that. I want to say thank you, Kelvia and Colin, and of course, Terry for allowing me to be part of us today. I got to sneak off here. And
Speaker 235: everyone that's watching too, there's a lot of people commenting on you.
Speaker 234: Yes. Yeah.
Speaker 154: Thanks everybody. Thank
Speaker 236: you. Thank you so much for
Speaker 154: joining us. Of course. Thanks Angela. Bye.
Speaker 176 (higher-pitched voice): Take care. Bye.
Speaker 79 (higher-pitched voice): Thank you so much.
The way
Speaker 79 (higher-pitched voice): that Angela and I have done by Angela, the way we have done our our our campaign is we both kind of do our own thing.
And
Speaker 73: so we we were good partners in that. So we don't do the same thing. Obviously, this was the same thing. So we get invited to different podcasts and things that we do virtually or in person. We've done.
Speaker 123: But large majority, we are two people going at it.
very
Speaker 123: independently together. We talk every single day, but, and as governor and lieutenant governor, I mean, we've, again, we're, our backgrounds are, you know, entrepreneurs, business owners, I'm a licensed therapist, community workers, right? Those are, so our brains work like that, right? It is,
Speaker 73: and when we think of the state and we think
of, you know,
Speaker 73: You know, my brain goes to how to develop what to do with what we have
in the
Speaker 73: best way that we can. It's not to raise taxes. It's to create lower cost of living, water security, all these things. Right. It's it's really about the people. And we do that with a mindset of, OK, this is what we have. And we have a lot and we have a lot that is.
Speaker 73: misused funds and all of this stuff that I think people, you know, full trans I want full transparency in our, in our, in our spending.
Speaker 75: It's not happening today in spending and transparency. It's just that it needs to and public taxpayer dollars.
Speaker 198: Yep. There's a swamp right here in Arizona. You know, they talk about the national swamp. You know, we have a swamp right here in Arizona. Yeah.
Speaker 238: Both. Most of the people are swimming in it.
A big one.
Speaker 239: Absolutely.
Speaker 15: Yeah. A big one.
One
Speaker 15: other thing I wanted to mention, you know, I love the
Speaker 131: fact that you're a health care worker, you know, licensed therapist, all that thing. You know, ironically, I think we need
Speaker 33: health care in politics.
I think
Speaker 33: we need people that have more emotional intelligence.
Speaker 92: And that brings me to another point. I'm kind of getting
Speaker 131: like Maha from you a little bit. I think the Maha Pack, I'm very familiar
Speaker 93: with the Maha Pack that works here in Arizona and they go up to D.C. and lobbyists.
Speaker 33: yeah the anti-vaxxers the mahal that that which is the healthy americans movement jfk yeah how do you how do you
feel where
Speaker 33: do you fit
Speaker 241: in in that room so
you know
Speaker 241: the the
Speaker 79 (higher-pitched voice): anti-vaccine thing right that people i think it should be a choice right
Speaker 123: vaccine's a choice um i can say in my during covid i my company's also medical so i'm not a medical provider but i have medical providers and in my
Speaker 123: company with uh employees uh we were state licensed so dhs licensed department of health services so they had rules but we did um where they could you know the religion or the health they could basically
not have to
Speaker 123: do it opt
Speaker 73: out right so you could opt out of the vaccine which i had many employees so nobody lost their job in my in my uh that's what i believe in right so if you
Speaker 123: choice okay choice in vaccines
um
Speaker 123: When it comes to behavioral health and what's happening in Arizona and the things that are happening here, you know, a lot of people don't realize how dire our health care system is today. I realize that people
Speaker 73: know that, you know, we can't afford it. I mean, for the first time in my life, I can't afford health insurance. I
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): mean, I'm paying two hundred dollars to just do emergency care. But it's cheaper. It's actually cheaper.
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): to to just do the emergency care but when when you're not and i work with a lot of people that could not do that could not do just emergency care because and we take all the insurance as well but it's you know you couldn't do emergency care because they can't um they have health problems right so most of america has health i mean not most but many americans have
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): health
Speaker 73: problems. They need health insurance to take care of them. And in Arizona, we have a big issue of being able to afford health care, but we also have a big issue with being able to find a provider that's going to take your insurance and that's going to serve you because providers today are going under. And
Speaker 123: we're talking thousands in any industry in the behavioral health, medical, they'll
Speaker 73: tell you it is...
Speaker 73: What's happening in Arizona is a crisis. We have a crisis on our hands right now regarding healthcare providers. And when I talk about that, I say that when providers are harmed, the patients are even more harmed. And that's the most disturbing part about it is people are going homeless without care.
Speaker 73: and so um you know i'm all for movements right movements in general that move that's part of the beauty of our country right because uh the things that people can do to help the people of
Speaker 243: our state nation and uh everything else yeah i'm
so glad
Speaker 124: you bring up health care because i think it's a national crisis
Speaker 124: Um, I had a friend that I talked
Speaker 93: to, I had a friend I talked to this morning. He is in Arizona. He went to urgent care, find out, found out how much it would cost for them to look at and then he went back home. He's like, I can't do this. And, um, they're actually getting treatment in Mexico.
Speaker 27: That's why I thought it was interesting. You said, you know, people throw over people over the border with ailments and
Speaker 33: sickness and stuff, but we have Americans going to Mexico and Canada.
Speaker 131: Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah.
And I
Speaker 131: think it's terrible. And I currently, you know, a lot of people don't have health insurance. And yeah, I think it's a huge issue. No one's really tapping into that, you know, even on the national level, other than lobbyists and stuff,
Speaker 62: you know, people aren't. I really wish Trump would look more into that with co-pays and health insurance plans and HMOs. Well,
Speaker 245: it's they're taking over. And I
Speaker 123: think a lot of people don't understand to like a provider
Speaker 73: standpoint and providers if they're listening to
Speaker 73: today or they'll know what I'm talking about. But for instance, what's happening today in Arizona, and I'm not sure again, if it's happening, I'm sure it's happening across the nation 'cause these big health plans,
Speaker 123: Optum, UHC, Cigna, Blue Cross, they are nationwide
as far as I'm
Speaker 123: concerned, or
Speaker 73: as far as I know. And, but in Arizona they're setting up little, not little, they're not little at all. They're setting
up,
Speaker 73: Clinics, OK, where if the patient goes to the clinic, they get as some of them, right, they'll get a zero copay for the same service that an in-network provider, the patient is charged $50. This is this is a real example of mine of patients. Right. So they come to me. I'm an in-network
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): provider. They pay $50 of a copay.
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): But, hey, if you go to this place and it's for employees, so I'll give you one hospital, for instance, Honor Health, OK, Honor Health goes, believe it's Honor Health, uses UnitedHealthcare, OK, as their employee, they used to use Magellan.
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): And, uh, that's one of the things that is then offered to the employee. Okay. You can just go here, you can go to this place and it's $0. Whereas in network provider. So what is that doing to in network providers? I mean, why do we, why is it, why is it fair? How is that not fraud? Right. How is that tip for tat where, uh,
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): Large, I mean,
Speaker 246 (higher-pitched voice): you're just they're just recycling the money back in. Why not? What I think is they should be offered zero copay for any in person or in network provider. Right. I mean, the patient, we're talking about access to care. Okay. Access to care is about the
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): patient, not about the money. And if the patient gets a $50 copay with me and then just offered, hey, if you go here, you can get zero. Well, then do
it.
For
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): me, they want to be with me, do zero dollar copay to be with me. I'm in network. Right. That's
Speaker 25: access to care. And that's really an interesting, I think I honestly think it's a type of fraud to be. I just don't understand how you could recycle the money back through your system. And that's just not fraud offering an incentive to go to your own place. Right. I'm going to give you literally it's like I'm going to give you fifty dollars in your pocket if you come here. when they're recycling
Speaker 25: the money back into Optum or Evernorth or any of these other places and that's a real-life example that's happening right now that's putting pushing providers out of network not wanting to take the the insurance and ultimately closing the doors of small providers
yeah I've
Speaker 170 (higher-pitched voice): heard a lot of
Speaker 34: holistic doctors and maha and healthy American people they drop health insurance all together
Speaker 34: And,
Speaker 93: um, also, I don't know if you've heard this in Arizona car insurance, which I think car insurance is a
Speaker 27: Ponzi scheme. I think health insurance is a Ponzi scheme. And I, they just, I've heard recently, Arizona is one of the worst, the highest rates of car insurance. Like it's really affecting people and it's
Speaker 73: become a big problem. Yeah. We have to stop the gouging of prices. And that's one thing that I'll do too, is the mazes behind that. So I heard recently talk.
Speaker 73: she is behind getting behind stopping the gouging of the prices that's occurring in our state. Minimum wage goes up and then people all
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): the everything goes up too. Everything goes up. I call it the system of keeping people poor. I watch my clients go through this and it is I've worked community mental health for many years and it is so sad because first off we want people to be off. People want
most
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): people want to have a job. Most people want to be part of society. Most people want to work and, you know, they're not, most people are, you know, it's a, they
just want to
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): make a living for their
Speaker 73: family, right? Pay their bills, have a home, have a roof over their head and have dinner on the table for their, for their family.
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): And, and
so when we
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): think about the things that are affecting people today, you know, this is, um,
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): We,
Speaker 123: we can't gouge prices, increase prices for people and keep it before. So
what I
Speaker 123: was going to say, it like went around my head for a second there. When people
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): come off benefits, right? The state benefits, oftentimes they become, they then get a job, they get
a job
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): and they get kicked off. It's this weird yo-yo, right? They're, they want to work. They want to work. Okay. And which helps our economy helps them, but then they're more poor, poor, right?
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): working because now they have to pay thousands of dollars to to have child care right all these things and so what do they do well they go back and afford it they can't afford it okay that we
Speaker 73: have to change and i will change that uh you know when we think about child care and creating programs for child care and and um i look at there's one state uh new mexico new mexico is the first state and the nation to do universal child care you don't do it right away you do it in a tiered
Speaker 73: system right
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): but doing that right now arizona can't even doesn't even have the i think they do but they are at a deficit of even providing
Speaker 73: the child care benefit to the families that that get it now in the system in the benefit system they're behind
so if we
Speaker 73: can create a program where people have more benefits including you know off-time work and rebates to employers small business
Speaker 73: create a program for, you know, eventually universal childcare and we'll start in different areas that there's a lack of childcare because rural, rural Arizona lacks childcare programs, we can reduce costs that way for people, right, and then ultimately creating some sort of program where you just don't get kicked off your benefits.
Speaker 73: It's like a tier program, right? You just you help people. I mean, the purpose is to help people. And if more people can enter the economy to work, our economy is better. And my experience is that most people want to work. One thing I want to tell people, too, that is scary about Andy Biggs is the SNAP benefit
Speaker 248: program. Our SNAP benefit program throughout the nation. Again, I say I look at what's happened federally. A lot of people blame federal. Listen, I look at, OK, that happened federally. Yeah, it's awful. So we,
Speaker 248: We took SNAP benefits and Medicaid program. Now, what do I do as a governor? Well, this is what I have to do. I don't I'm not going to complain about that and focus on what I don't have.
Speaker 142 (higher-pitched voice): I'm going to focus on what I do. OK, so here's what I have and here's what I'm going to do. And the thing is, is that Andy Biggs, it's loaded on his website. This is a guy that.
you
Speaker 142 (higher-pitched voice): know, one, I don't know, what is that? The sweepstakes or
Speaker 25: whatever, like $10 million or something. I mean, he has no clue what normal Americans go through, right? In my opinion, go through in Arizona, let alone ever sit at the table with somebody who is suffering, right?
Like, or
Speaker 25: struggling to pay their bills, right? Give me a break. He's never done that. And yet he wants to
Speaker 25: Um, will not allow for people to heal. He'll dictate what they can spend their money on. Now, some people say that's
Speaker 141 (higher-pitched voice): great. They should only be allowed to buy, um, you know, uh, greens and all these things. And I'm like, okay, no,
no.
who
Speaker 141 (higher-pitched voice): okay i get that idea but when we come back to the maha movement right and the nutrition
what i
Speaker 141 (higher-pitched voice): say to people okay you're going to provide them a nutritionist because access medicaid does not provide that nutritionist i know that firsthand because i had dietitians in my company i don't anymore but they're not they don't pay by insurance medicaid does not pay for that so
you're
Speaker 141 (higher-pitched voice): know how to eat or you're going to tell them how to eat you're
Speaker 142 (higher-pitched voice): just going to do away and many people have told me terry i don't want my benefits to be controlled by the government because i have diabetes and i don't know about if you guys know this but i do as a health care provider if you ever see those signs on the side of the
Speaker 141 (higher-pitched voice): street that says um i have insulin needles i have insulin okay the reason why that happens is because literally people cannot get their medication and stuff happening for whatever reason. I've seen those recently. Okay. Absolutely.
Speaker 141 (higher-pitched voice): because they can't get their medication for and they have diabetes they need their insulin okay so i've had people say i don't have any money this is i use snap every i don't i carry a candy bar in my purse and i have diabetes right and i'm like
I get
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): it. That's not for everyone. But why are we going to control the spending of if you give them three hundred dollars or whatever they get? Right. For a
Speaker 123: benefit, allow them to buy what they want to buy. Right. And I had a person. It was actually a reporter. And it's
Speaker 250: also about freedom. You know, we're not slaves. We're not supposed to be treated as slaves. Well, I want to
Speaker 1: I want
to I
Speaker 1: want to bring out one more thing, too, about that is, you know,
A lot of
Speaker 1: things they don't realize, too, is two things. One, you know, eating right, eating those, like,
greens and
Speaker 1: eating stuff that's healthy is a lot more expensive than eating, you know, junk food or whatever. And secondly, like, people that are, like, they're not even considering the extremely large homeless
Speaker 111: population where homeless people don't have access to be able to cook and, you know, make those kind of meals and stuff. So that's all they can eat
Speaker 176 (higher-pitched voice): is...
Speaker 176 (higher-pitched voice): A salad.
Speaker 111: Exactly. I mean,
we have
Speaker 176 (higher-pitched voice): bigger problems in controlling people from getting a soda pop. I mean, my goodness, they have life. I mean,
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): they're probably they're dealing with life difficulties. And if they want to buy a soda, I had a she may be listening to a reporter who is a good friend of mine now, too. I'm not
Speaker 123: going to name her, but she gave an example of
a
A
Speaker 123: family. Right. We had this conversation. She's she would agree with me on this. She gave the example of I walked into a Burger King and a mother bought her children dinner using SNAP benefits. Right.
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): And. I, you know, I look at that and say,
well,
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): that is they sat down for a dinner right that might be all they can afford and they got to go to dinner i have that to me is shouldn't be taken away from people right that shouldn't be taken away from these families and we shouldn't the government shouldn't control whether or not they could buy
it uh
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): so what i say okay is why not create a a a point system okay if they buy the
uh
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): you know if we want to do anything create in the world of behavioral health okay we call it a paddle versus a a carrot how to change behavior okay uh i had a
Speaker 123: teacher one time tell me an example of this in a internship i did a long time ago and he said he used to he put a big donkey on the board i was a mental health therapist intern and he goes now the paddle gets the donkey moving right right
Speaker 123: this is the the distinction of behavioral change right uh and but the
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): carrot gets the donkey moving on its own right and so when we think about people right obviously not there we aren't donkeys people but we think of it in
Speaker 123: the if we the behavioral reward system a reward versus a punitive action taking away always creates a better change right
And
Speaker 123: it's again, it's research based. It's it's part of how I we work in systems work and stuff like that. It's a behavioral health approach,
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): but you don't punish. OK, you don't take away and punish people. In addition, a white rich man. OK, telling me, you know, telling people how to eat.
I mean,
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): come on.
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): There are grocery stores. Andy Biggs lives in Gilbert, right? Gilbert's one of the richest cities in Arizona. Okay. And if you, it is well known, it's research. There are supermarkets that only sell certain things. Okay. Based on the demographic. Okay. So a rich white man telling people how to eat off their benefit program is I think cruel and unnecessary.
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): And I think just and he says it like, I'm going to do that. I mean, it's like you don't even get it. You don't even get it. Right. You're so aloof to the need of the people. It's not about forcing them. I mean, who let them have a soda? And,
you
Speaker 131: know, it's not the population has changed. You
Speaker 92: know, I have a couple of.
I
Speaker 92: have a college degree and I can't, which means nothing essentially to me, it doesn't. And I can't afford healthy food all the time.
Speaker 59: I know it's expensive. I would love to see the American population obesity rates go down. I would love to see diabetes go down and heart disease. I would love to see people eat chicken and broccoli every night for dinner. Yeah. They don't want it. Yeah.
Speaker 170 (higher-pitched voice): They don't want it, but it's also just not in the cards. I mean, if you want to buy a, you know, broccoli and chicken, that's
Speaker 56 (higher-pitched voice): expensive. Correct. Yeah. So, so, yeah, so, you know, we could
Speaker 123: create a point like a, so with that, that model of, and I'm not saying I would do this, but this is an example of what you could do to help people to purchase, you know, more healthy foods. You could do a point system. You get, you know, two points for this, one point for this and those types of things. So they actually get more,
you know,
for
Speaker 123: what they're buying right because we know that even groceries that are um healthy right i mean
come
Speaker 113: on a salad can be the worst thing today okay how much dressing to put on it i mean it can be one of the worst things you can
Speaker 254: eat today if it's iceberg it has no nutrition in the first place correct and
Speaker 113: people want to
Speaker 79 (higher-pitched voice): buy the food that they want to buy for their family and i just think that that's just anyways we could do a point system you know that could actually increase the amount We have thought about
Speaker 73: farmers markets
and helping
Speaker 73: small business and those things also.
So I
Speaker 73: look at a reward system versus a punitive system of, of, of helping people. And ultimately, you
Speaker 123: know, if, if we're going to just, if we're going to control people's spending, right. I mean, I don't know. I just think it's, I
think it's
Speaker 243: one of the cruelest things he's put out so far, but I mean, he's just,
he's a
Speaker 243: cruel. I agree.
Speaker 255: Here's the thing. I may be a little worried,
You
Speaker 33: know, I may be a little wacko, but, you know, I think the government would ultimately like us to be dependent on them. And, you know, there's a couple of things that they do. I'm a millennial. A lot of us are
Speaker 256: still in
Speaker 27: school debt. I think that, you know, unemployment in Arizona is just a couple hundred dollars a week, if that happens.
So
Speaker 93: they make it to where if you work or if you work a part-time job, you're not going to get unemployment. If you
Speaker 59: make a certain amount in a year, you can't get assistance, but it's not really enough to live either. So they put you in a rock in a hard place and to where you either
Speaker 257: have to be fully dependent on them.
Speaker 257: They
Speaker 110: incentivize you. Yeah, they incentivize you not to work. That's how the system is set up.
And
Speaker 150: it just and people want to work.
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): I will tell you that most people want to work and they want to be self-sufficient. They don't want to utilize benefits, but they should be allowed. Let's just talk about our elderly.
Speaker 73: Right. So.
Speaker 73: If we focus on the elderly, I watched again, I'm a native here. My grandparents, my family's from Iowa. So but I'm a
Speaker 18: native in Arizona. My sister and I and the I don't know
why I
Speaker 18: said that, but it doesn't matter. My grandparents who are here, I watch them
and.
Speaker 18: pass away from my grandma from Alzheimer's. My grandpa ended up dying in 2020 from COVID. But he, both of them, it
Speaker 81: took years, or my grandma had Alzheimer's. It took her, it took us like two or three years before she was almost on her deathbed to get benefits of all techs, right? For
Speaker 18: help. My grandpa, same thing. I mean, falling on
his head,
Speaker 18: flooded, not able to do anything, and finally able to get benefits. We're talking about families can afford cost of living, but also then their loved ones can't get benefits on time. So I want to change the assessment tools for people regarding all tax and benefit
Speaker 25: programs so that you don't have to be six months of dead in order to get it like I watched both my grandparents go through.
And
Speaker 25: that's happening in our state too, and I watch it as a therapist as well. People get denied this benefit
left and right.
Speaker 110: Absolutely, I actually was denied, I'm disabled myself. I was denied three different times for disability. I still don't have disability. That's why I do the
Speaker 1: online thing, and this is basically my job now.
Speaker 1: And thank God I was able to do that. But yeah, I mean, I'm disabled and I should be able to get disability. But the system is set up to where,
you know, they
Speaker 5: intentionally build in denying you. And that's so wrong that they do that. You know, basically you have to have a lawyer in order to even get a chance at getting disabilities.
approved
Speaker 5: for disability and it's a very long tedious process that a lot of people just don't want to go through
yeah it's
Speaker 22: the same thing in arizona that's happening too it's just it's really disgusting to be honest with
you we um
Speaker 22: people people
Speaker 14: are suffering and i know it's happening nationwide arizona we are um you know people are suffering and and i can say you know the what i say to people all the
time
Speaker 22: is i i know suffering you know i i'm in recovery eight you
Speaker 22: 18 years drugs and alcohol right got sober at 23 it's hard it was nothing easy about that process um
Speaker 18: and you know i think that
Speaker 258: says i don't suffer today
Speaker 260: about that actually what i wanted to i actually wanted to ask
you about that yeah i
Speaker 262: wanted to just kind of tell us your story or whatever
yeah
Oh,
Speaker 263 (higher-pitched voice): yeah. Oh, yeah. So I started using drugs. My
Speaker 25: dad died of alcoholism. My dad and grandpa died six days apart in 2020. We don't believe it's both COVID. But my dad died of alcoholism 2020. I grew up with, you know, grew up in that for a long time. And so at 10 years old and started using drugs and alcohol around 14 years.
Speaker 25: 10 started drinking and 14 started using drugs. And so the, you know, my life path was a path of, of, of darkness really, until I was 23 and gave my life to Christ. And it was a hard, hard life. And it was a point where, you know, many, you know, I say a lot of times
Speaker 19: I'm so grateful that not wasn't around back then. Cause I don't think I'd be here today. But yeah,
Speaker 19: Uh, fentanyl is just a crazy, crazy happening. Uh, and that's a whole nother breed, but devastating.
Speaker 264: Absolutely. It's
Speaker 19: devastating. My, um,
and, and
Speaker 263 (higher-pitched voice): so, you know, for me, it was seeing, uh, really believing that
I
Speaker 18: was going to die and throwing it all away. And,
um,
um it was
Speaker 18: like uh you know i got i had to get rid of my house i had to move back home at 23 years old you know it was kind of like this uh i um went into the restaurant field finished my degrees uh and just but it was a struggle i tell people all the time you know that's why i went to working with people in substance abuse that was my primary thing and then uh i'm a licensed therapist and so too but the um uh
Speaker 18: that's one of the most heartbreaking things and why i'm here today too when when when i think about uh people going through recovery and they don't have places to go today in areas i mean it's just it's it's so providers are scared to serve medicaid and other plans and they should be they should be okay because at any moment what happened to me can happen to them and it's happening
i'm
Speaker 18: Every single day to more providers and it's just horrible what's happening and and and ultimately we're going to get to a state where these people won't have, you know, people like me back then don't have the ability to get help and
so.
Um,
Speaker 18: it, that's, you know, the, the really just seeing, um, and mental health, right? So mental health. And so I've, I've really focused on lowering stigma and mental health. I've done a lot of events where I've talked, I talk about suicide prevention, my dissertation
Speaker 25: for my PhD, I did in Louisiana. Um, it was in a detention center for children.
Speaker 18: adolescent sex offenders so my dissertations on quality of life of uh or was on quality life of uh adolescent sex offenders it
was my
Speaker 18: uh it was very interesting right to to to to understand the quality of life and what one of the things i say on my run here is saying you know ultimately and i i want people to have what if every one of us have a different way of life right
but
Speaker 18: everyone can have an improved quality of life of whatever that means for each one of us. And I think that that is possible. Okay. That is possible. I know it's possible. And then, you know, one of the, that was
one of
Speaker 18: the greatest things and struggles in my life was getting sober. I, I do tell people it took about five years to feel normal. And, um, yeah, like five years, I struggle bad. Um, and, um, but
yeah,
You
Speaker 18: know, my program was I did 12 step, you know, 12 subsequent program. And then church was a big, big thing for me. God. Right. And then and then the most difficult thing that's surpassed my life now is is the recent thing that happened to me in 2023. Right. Being accused of fraud and then taking two years and seven days to clear my
name.
Speaker 18: Uh, but ultimately, you know, here I am running for governor. I know I wouldn't be here today
if it
Speaker 18: wasn't for nine 22, 2023. And I'll tell you something cool. The, um, Erica, uh, Angela,
Speaker 25: my running mate, uh, I was introduced by her because I, we both, uh, are friends with somebody who, um,
Speaker 25: She also, her name's Ashley, but if anybody knows Ryan, so you can Google that name. Ryan. So as a DPS officer in Scottsdale, he passed away a few years ago in the line of duty. It was a accidental shooting of his gun firing off, but that's how they knew each other. And then I reached out to her, Ashley and said, which is his widow and said, who's
Speaker 19: doing great today, by the way, but the,
um,
And
Speaker 19: said, hey, if you know anyone, I need somebody to be lieutenant
Speaker 263 (higher-pitched voice): governor I'm interviewing. I really want somebody that is not a politician, is like me in community service, just wants to be part of helping. You know, I didn't want anybody with like tentacles in to places. And she texts me and said, I have this person. Oh my gosh, she'd be perfect.
Speaker 263 (higher-pitched voice): And so I talked to her that day and we met and we met in person, Angela and I, and her
Speaker 25: birthday is 922, which is the date that all this happened with me. Right. 922, 2023. So I was like, oh, my gosh, this is so.
That's a
Speaker 265: sign. And then within 24
Speaker 263 (higher-pitched voice): hours, I mean, literally a meeting, she's like, I'm going to do it with you. And so we're like, yes, let's do it. You know,
Speaker 25: we're really just we're two people that.
Speaker 25: are highly driven and to help people. And we're competent in this area in entrepreneurship and business. But think about, and oftentimes people say, oh, your business, and this happens, you know, Mike,
look,
Speaker 25: I steered this business in three years to not, it's not gone under, right? There's something that I've done as an entrepreneur business person that has kept this business up and going, despite all of this has happened. And,
Speaker 18: you know, that's unfortunate. Unfortunately for many people who are good owners, you know,
Speaker 18: and good entrepreneurs have lost their businesses so i don't say that in a way that says look at me i did this and they're bad right
Speaker 25: what i'm doing today is to help people uh who have lost their businesses many of them my friends and um and i'm deeply connected to the community of mental health and and many people know me in the community and um and what is happening today is heartbreaking
Speaker 25: heartbreaking to me that our community and mental health and and um is just being harmed and it's being harmed because katie hobbs is doing nothing and i say that because her agency's
Speaker 25: are the state agencies including the medicaid program des you know while they had their snap benefit des conference they spent two hundred thousand dollars on a conference you can they can google that just recently happened uh not recent a few months ago i talked about my site
at the very same
Speaker 25: time they're literally having this conference every director of des department of economic security katie hobbs is there it's like i'm not there it was online she posted about and all this stuff, I just thought this is so disgusting
Speaker 263 (higher-pitched voice): because
we,
Speaker 263 (higher-pitched voice): you were there with donors and influence and all this stuff asked, you know, Oh, look how great Arizona is. What? There's all these articles. People are not getting paid their benefits right now. Nope. They're not getting their snap benefits. And
Speaker 25: you're literally having a conference about, I mean, and at the very same time, and that's how disconnected.
Katie
Speaker 25: Hobbs is, is from the
harm
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): and Medicaid is her agency. And so tell me, and I, I believe, and I've said this before publicly that,
Speaker 248: uh, that there is, there is massive, uh, racketeering and money laundering happening in our Medicaid system. That is my belief. Okay. I'm not saying that's a fact.
Speaker 266: That is my absolute
Speaker 248: belief in what is happening. And I've talked about it, you know, and I've talked about things that are happening and what I believe is happening. And because there's just no explanation for why this
Speaker 248: is happening to arizona's um and the providers because people need to understand that despite the federal government
Speaker 81: giving money to the states for medicaid um in order for that money to be deposited
Speaker 73: we have to do a service so what happens is
And
Speaker 73: the world of Medicaid, a provider such as myself does a service that service stimulates the response from Medicaid state, but also federal to give the money. Right. Give the money. Now, when the provider is cut off and not paid, they owe
Speaker 263 (higher-pitched voice): me a million over a million dollars. OK, so and the for services rendered and they
Speaker 141 (higher-pitched voice): they they have this money. OK, it's not theirs. It's the providers. It's
not
Speaker 267 (higher-pitched voice): their money.
Now
Speaker 267 (higher-pitched voice): they cut the provider off for years and they have this
Speaker 246 (higher-pitched voice): money.
It's just
Speaker 246 (higher-pitched voice): like, where's the money? That's Katie Hobbs. It's owed to the provider. Okay. And of course, I'm not...
And
Speaker 246 (higher-pitched voice): the people committing fraud, they need to be
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): prosecuted. They need to be prosecuted faster. Okay. Fraud needs to be prosecuted. And I'm not, you know, one of the things I'll do in the Medicaid system is bring
Speaker 25: independent reviews immediately in, remove the public, public hanging systems that we have, which that's my opinion of those, their public
Speaker 248: list suspension exclusion that demonizes providers before they're ever even, they're, it's just an allegation. the state Senate said, or the,
Speaker 248: Vanessa Templeton, who's the inspector general of the OIG, says in a testimony 10-1-2025 in the Senate hearing, says 71% of providers, that's her number. I use
it all
Speaker 248: the time because it's mind-boggling. 71% of providers are innocent that this happens to, but they
do it
Speaker 248: because of an administrative
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): burden. Administrative burden, they shut the providers down because it's too burdensome to... When I got shut down, you guys, I...
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): people don't understand that when provider is suspended 80% of my business was medicated when a provider is my payroll was 1.1 million a month to my 250 staff
Speaker 81: when they suspend a provider you are required by law to continue to provide services that is suspended payment to the to the patients okay so for four months I continued to provide services to thousands of patients
and
no
Speaker 81: payment to me
Speaker 14: but i paid my staff and then i had to discharge the patient which we did over the course of four months um we didn't just drop the patients and many patients
Speaker 248: are still with us and they are pro bono today medicaid but um some
of them
Speaker 123: but uh they are if they're still with us right
but it's
Speaker 56 (higher-pitched voice): it's a lot of
Speaker 268: your staff too which is absolutely disgusting you know
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): Yes. And now when I got cleared immediately, when I got cleared, they should have all those health plans. So in Arizona, there's a Medicaid hub and then there are seven managed care plans. One of the things I want to do is what we used to have was one plan.
Speaker 81: Okay. It's become a pro system for pro money and it's access to care is diminished. Okay.
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): In our state, we need one Medicaid plan. It makes it easier for providers, easier for patients.
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): Then, you know, as soon as I'm clear two days, you know, two years and seven days, they should have paid me immediately. Okay. Only
two of
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): the plans paid me. Okay. Only two. I had to file lawsuit, which is in place now against the five other plans, but they push it. What they do is they push it to arbitration, which costs people an arm and a leg. I mean, it's like you owe me the money for rendered services. And I just got let go. And I'm just like, and this has
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): happening to thousands of providers, but they're, they're, it's shame.
Speaker 248: And, um, that covers these providers that they don't speak out and I don't blame them. And that I, I use my voice to carry that. I, honestly, I lived in shame for two years until I started speaking on social media, because when you experience this level of shame that you're accused of something you didn't
do,
Speaker 248: that's why I'm so big on due process. Uh, I, I can't tell, I can't explain to people unless it's happened. I say oftentimes the only other thing that would be worse than this is losing a child. Um, but, and I won't, I won't relate that to that. Cause I don't think that that's the
same pain,
Speaker 248: but even today, when I walk into my clinic, I
have two
Speaker 248: clinics, but I shut down five and I was telling Colin this the other day, I said, when I just sold some furniture, right. And, um,
Speaker 248: And every piece of furniture I sell, it's like, oh, my gosh, it hurts. Three years I held on to this, you guys, three years believing that this this
Speaker 25: would change for me. And again, I don't say that for pity. I don't. But this is ultimately where I've come. And this is why I'm here. Right. Is because people are suffering, not just providers, but then we talk about.
Speaker 25: People with disabilities and, you know, cost of living and all these things just in, you know, there's a full blanket of people suffering and I, I'm so sick and, and the government not listening, not listening, not caring about us.
And
Speaker 25: it's just infuriating to me that I could never get a hold of Chris Mays or Katie Hobbs to help me like
Speaker 248: nothing. A senator tried to help me, but you couldn't go past the governor's seat. And again, I think there was money involved and there was racketeering and money laundering. That's my belief. That's what it's
Speaker 269: about. That's
Speaker 270: what I'll find when I'm governor. I know it. I mean, there's just no explanation for this. It's just like crazy.
they were
Speaker 270: probably none of them probably slept at night when i won the primary they're probably like oh my god she freaking
won
Speaker 271: she actually did it by god she actually this is not a joke
when you when you have
Speaker 103: truth and god on your side you're unstoppable
Speaker 176 (higher-pitched voice): Romans 8 31 is against me. Yeah. I'm like, that's a scripture I keep using
Speaker 248: to them. And I need people to understand that, you know, I'm like, I'm, I'm for separation church and state just because I share my personal belief doesn't mean I bring it into politics and my decision making. I still look at everything as fair and judicial,
Speaker 75: but Jesus is the love of my life. So it's
Speaker 160: like, I, I do talk about him. I mean, but it is an interesting
story.
I
Speaker 160: can't do any
Speaker 275: wrong bringing God into things.
Speaker 123: Yeah. It's just, it's just personal for me, you know, it's okay. The people have beliefs and that's okay. And, and
Speaker 134: yeah. So, well,
Speaker 276: Terry, it has been an absolute pleasure.
Speaker 27: I've really enjoyed this. I've been looking at the chat and it looks like that you have some votes. Thanks. Yeah. Thanks
Speaker 277: everyone for, for, for chatting. you can reach out to me,
my number
Speaker 277: is actually on my website so you can call me and text me
um at
Speaker 277: any point
um and the
Speaker 5: website uh her website is linked in the description of the video for everybody uh and in the post so if you want to if you want to check out our website go ahead
Sorry,
Speaker 63 (higher-pitched voice): let me just say one more thing before you close out. We
Speaker 73: will do a day one moratorium on data centers. So that is not again, we're not against data centers, we're against what is what's happening in the community with data centers, and water and energy and ensure we're and
Speaker 75: before they go. And we're the only ones that will say that because we're the only ones not bought off by them.
Okay, one and done.
well
Speaker 10: thank you for that um is there any we're not we're not just gonna we're not just gonna shut down is there okay
yeah
Speaker 278: we're not just gonna
Speaker 10: okay oh
wait you just went
Speaker 270: out i can't hear you oh oh there now
i
Speaker 279: can't
Speaker 270: yeah okay okay um is there any
Speaker 92: other closing statements that you would like to tell constituents of arizona um anything you just want them to know you
know
yeah
Speaker 92: take a chance
Speaker 63 (higher-pitched voice): you
Speaker 241: know
Speaker 281: yeah and
i
Speaker 63 (higher-pitched voice): think just for your vote right like go out vote be a part of you know a lot of i know um there's a lot of talk on whether or not we should vote
Speaker 248: this year and
you know i
Speaker 248: hear people talk about and vote this year in arizona especially if
Speaker 73: you're wanting an investigation a deeper investigation charlie kirk assassination of course we can't investigate the murder but if anything happened in the planning stages here we can investigate that here and I will and I've already stood on that
Speaker 73: And in addition, looking at what's happening in TPUSA, which is I believe it's the largest organization donation right now into our political system. I could be wrong on that, but I think it is. And
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): then, you know, and take a chance. You need to realize that Andy Biggs and Katie Hobbs are both evil again, my opinion, but.
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): and you know it's a it's a coin flip on who's worse for our states so I just need everyone because some people are like but Annie Biggs is worse or Katie Hobbs we're like look they are both horrible okay if they if they weren't we would
Speaker 123: be in a better place today they both had opportunity to help us they both had opportunity to save us they both had opportunity to affect change in Arizona
and
Speaker 73: they both have failed Arizona failed okay so we have to stand up we have to vote
for
Speaker 73: Um, and I don't say how you don't have to, but you know, we,
I
Speaker 248: want change. I really feel scared if one of them are elected and, um, and what could happen further in Arizona. So here I am trying my best. I said, I'd rather, uh, lose or try and fail than not try at all. So,
and I
Speaker 123: really think Arizona don't go, don't go off the, um, the polls, they are rigged.
they
Speaker 123: are they don't even have me on there so how could
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): we judge me based on
Speaker 282: exactly and
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): by the way i was not on the polls in the primary my opponent was probably because he had so much money and guess who won me so
the polls do not
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): matter okay so i don't know i'm gonna find out what's going on with the polls too because in arizona i think we should have fair people
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): Need to know that in Arizona and across our nation, there are laws in place regarding fairness to politicians and candidates
Speaker 81: in office. And it's just not our candidates running. It's not happening. It's not happening. How is that fair that a poll can run in Arizona
Speaker 248: and not place everyone on there? It's like. So it's fine. That's fine.
Speaker 283: Well, completely
Speaker 284: wrong.
What
Speaker 283: I want to say is I love.
I live
Speaker 283: in Arizona. We
Speaker 170 (higher-pitched voice): both live in Glendale. Yay, Glendale. I don't hear that too often. That's my city. I tell people that's my city. It was my first home here in Arizona. It's my
Speaker 286: city. Yeah, mine too.
But
Speaker 92: Arizonians, listen up. I love what Terry said. Please take a chance. Take a leap of faith. You know, she's a believer.
Speaker 92: And we all need to believe we all need to bring God
Speaker 27: back into politics, you know, and take a chance. I'm speaking to independents. I'm speaking to Mahal Healthy Americans. I'm speaking to those that don't feel motivated to go out and vote because you're like, who do I vote for?
Or
Speaker 27: the less of the two evils. Well, we have we have someone right in the middle. We have someone who's open minded, who thinks you should abide by the law. You know, she's a conservative. She has conservative values. And for those that feel betrayed by MAGA, you know, Andy Biggs is endorsed is endorsed by Trump, you know, depending on how you feel about the current administration. You know, but those of you that feel betrayed, you feel like you've been
Speaker 62: lied to
him.
Speaker 62: Those of you that were huge Charlie Kirk fans and believe in freedom of
Speaker 27: speech and you think what's going on with the Tyler Robinson case is just awful and you believe in due process and innocent until proven guilty. You know, if you if you
Speaker 60: don't like the corruption in Arizona and all the big donors and all this big money that's influencing it, you know, this is your chance. This is the this is the chance that you can take to make a change on things.
Speaker 60: And, you know, if you don't like what Turning Point is doing as a whole organization in Arizona, you know, this is another chance, you know, maybe there'll
be some
Speaker 60: justice, you know,
Speaker 93: maybe, you know, maybe we can actually hold some people accountable for things. So Terry, Terry is a great option.
Speaker 290: She is a great alternative to Arizona.
And you
Speaker 290: have my full support. Thank you.
Speaker 260: Likewise, you have mine as well. Thank you, guys.
Thank you.
Speaker 5: And we have one more thing that we just want to close out with real quick. We're going to give you guys a little treat here. This is a I just want to show you kind of Tyler Boyer's character for one. We have a video of Tyler Boyer. You want to give
us the context
Speaker 5: for it, Kelvia? I
just someone
Speaker 293: commented this under one of his posts. I'd never seen this video.
I
Speaker 11: believe it's just kind of funny. It looks like someone's wearing like a body cam and they're speaking to him directly. But it's an interesting clip.
Speaker 294: I think he's trying to claim that he didn't endorse anybody. So it's funny. Carrie Lake. He's
Speaker 110: trying to endorse. He didn't endorse Carrie
Lake when
Speaker 110: he did. And this woman is putting him.
Putting him
Speaker 110: on the on the on the coals.
Speaker 110: Yeah, she's putting him on the coals, and it's fun to watch him squirm here. But you can just tell just what a bad liar he is. But it's just something else. This
Speaker 296: is what you're up against. Exactly,
Speaker 110: exactly. Because he's the
Speaker 111: one that's behind, like I said, he's the one that's behind Biggs. Yep, so he's exactly who you're going after right here.
You're funny for
Speaker 297: showing this.
All
Speaker 298: right, here we go.
Speaker 299: It's all the way back,
Speaker 302: what are
Speaker 304: you talking about?
Speaker 302: Okay. All right.
Speaker 304: Sorry, I can't hear you.
It's all the way back.
I
Speaker 299: haven't put anything
Speaker 305: out that I endorsed her. Other people have.
So
Speaker 299: you're saying that Carrie
Speaker 306: deceitfully put your name on there? I don't think it
was
Speaker 307: Carrie. I think it was somebody else.
Speaker 308: Well you said up there that Carrie did.
When
Speaker 307: Denise
Speaker 308: asked you.
Speaker 309 (lower-pitched voice): She showed me a graphic that Carrie put out.
Speaker 309 (lower-pitched voice): So I think somebody else put out that I endorsed her. I haven't publicly endorsed anyone. I retweeted graphics and things like that. That's it.
Speaker 310: - Retweeted graphics with your name endorsing her? - Yeah. - That's you endorsing her.
Speaker 309 (lower-pitched voice): - Oh, you can parse
Speaker 311: words, but I haven't endorsed anybody in this race.
Speaker 312: - Yeah, but you're sitting here-- - The presidency called me yesterday
Speaker 311: and said,
hey,
Speaker 311: do you like Gina? I said, I love Gina.
Speaker 313: Do you like Jim? I said, I love Jim. Jim's not asked me to support her. But here's my thing.
Speaker 314: And then the other thing I said to you is when you told people that the hand can had just been
Speaker 315: done, you made it seem as if that's what the hand can is like. I misspoke and you can crucify me for that. Well, it's not
Speaker 318: about crucifying you. It's you identifying it was just completely misleading that room of people who wasn't. I immediately
Speaker 319: corrected it as
Speaker 319: I didn't hear it. Well, you didn't. You were too busy. You want to be angry at me. I
Speaker 320: wasn't angry. I'm not angry with you now. I want accountability. I want
Speaker 321: truth. And I said, and
Speaker 322: I said, "Card kit."
Speaker 323: I read, I read. You need to make that clear. Yeah, because you didn't. Because if it was actually... Yeah,
Speaker 324: but I'm trying to help you guys out. Who do you
Speaker 325: think organized... What
do you
Speaker 325: think about
Speaker 326: that, Terry?
Speaker 72: Yeah, I mean, it just it
Speaker 135: really disturbs, you know, me and how people I think the biggest thing that disturbs me about that is that
Speaker 123: they claim to be what they are. Right. They claim to be Christian. They claim to be godly. They claim that, you know, that's probably what what disturbs me the most. And then again, it's just this lying to people. Right. And this facade, you know, if I
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): was you know, we know in Arizona, they put out Turning Point USA, put out these
stories.
for
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): bigs or uh democrats for bigs and you know i even think i think that's wrong i've talked against it i'm independent i'm running against democrat uh katie hobbs but i still think it's
wrong i
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): think it's wrong i think it's wrong that
Speaker 79 (higher-pitched voice): they're gonna lie to people regardless of the fact
that i
Speaker 79 (higher-pitched voice): don't think it's funny to lie to people even though it's a you know it's essentially going against katie hobbs i still think it's bad right i don't want i don't want people to be lied to
Speaker 79 (higher-pitched voice): and misled. And if I was, if that was my
Speaker 73: company doing that, right, and they were putting out these signs, and they were caught for it, or putting out AI that projected Democrats, and they perhaps may be sued by the Democratic Party, I don't know, that was in articles, but for doing it, but I would publicly say as the CEO, i.e.
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): Erica Kirk, I would
say,
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): you know i would publicly apologize if i was a candidate and that happened
Speaker 25: and they were doing that with my science i would publicly say i did not i was not okay with this none of that is happening with bigs and that is what people need to realize that these people are just as behind it in my opinion you know they think it's funny to lie to people they think it's funny to to to lie to arizonans and and people around i mean just to win the race it's just disgusting right just
Speaker 327: When at all costs.
Speaker 327: absolutely it's
Speaker 25: just
Speaker 252: power and they'll tell you they'll tell you that other people lie and then they lie to you i mean just like how are you okay with
Speaker 135: this you know um yeah and and i don't know money money is
money the root
Speaker 135: of all evil
Speaker 328: people do
Speaker 123: weird stuff with money right and
um so it's
Speaker 123: just really
Speaker 329: disturbing all
of it
Speaker 177 (higher-pitched voice): But I'm like, this is what I'm running against and it's
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): OK because I had to get to a place in my life, you know, when I finally started speaking out, when I lost everything, I lost everything at that
Speaker 73: point, you know, and everything
in the
Speaker 73: aspect of a thing in my business. Right. This baby I grew and and and then I started speaking out and the shame started falling as I started speaking and and then just realizing that.
you
Speaker 73: know people are hurting we have to have truth we have to have justice in arizona and and then
Speaker 248: ultimately i had to get to a place where i didn't give a i didn't give a shit anymore i'm just gonna
Speaker 123: say that you know like i mean there's no other word good
of a
Speaker 123: crap you know uh excuse my language but the you know i didn't give a crap
Speaker 79 (higher-pitched voice): and oh the
the um
Speaker 79 (higher-pitched voice): uh, retaliation, all these things that
Speaker 73: can happen and do happen. The government retaliates. I experienced it firsthand. Um, and, and I, and I had to get
in a
Speaker 73: place where it just, it's, I'm
not going to
Speaker 73: shut up.
I'm not
Speaker 73: going to shut up.
Speaker 73: and you're not going to force me to shut up and i'm not going to stop talking i'm not defamatory i'm not like you know i'm not speaking untruth i'm speaking opinion and experience and i'm trying to help people and it's just alarming the fact that they you know i talk about justin lum in arizona he's with fox 10 justin lum and i talk about him i just posted some stuff last night and i i called him out privately but
also i
Speaker 73: publicly call him out as well because whistleblowers say that he's part of a system of what's happening to providers in Arizona regarding, and again, I don't know if this is true, but then he blocked me on all the apps. A reporter blocks me
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): on all the apps. So I think that's wildly interesting that Justin
Lum
I
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): say, hey, this whistleblower said that you're getting paid off to shut down to help competitive providers shut down providers in the state of Arizona by doing stories. Mind you, this is very personal to me in doing stories on providers that are being crucified by the state, have not been convicted, have an allegation of fraud, were wrongfully terminated, excluded, suspended, no due process. You go to their door, you do these things,
you put your
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): your head this is his recent post right and i'm like you're so disgusting like you're hurting people you're hurting people tell me why the last three years i've reached and he did it to me he did it to me too and
Speaker 79 (higher-pitched voice): now i'm innocent right i'm an innocent provider he did that too and like i just
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): find it so alarming and so infuriating and then i find out there's whistleblowers who come to me and others that
um
Say
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): he's actually getting paid off, okay, this is what they say, to do stories like this and not other, and that would explain why for three years, he wouldn't do a story with me, you won't even talk to me, you won't do a story about what's happening to providers, right, so again, when we talk about why people shut you out and just silence you,
it's
I just
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): find that pretty interesting. Right. If it's not true, then it's not true. But like, why are you and there's an affidavit of a whistleblower that is signed that says that this happened. OK. And as governor, I will find it out. And he's an employee of Fox 10 and I will ensure that he loses his job. I
mean,
Speaker 267 (higher-pitched voice): end of story. You want to hurt people by your stupid little stories?
Speaker 267 (higher-pitched voice): OK, your fake news. OK, that's why I call it fake news.
OK, they
Speaker 267 (higher-pitched voice): are
Speaker 331: fake news, fake
Speaker 267 (higher-pitched voice): news. And stop
Speaker 123: doing that to people and hurting people just alone. I hope you hear that. Somebody tell me because he blocked
Speaker 88: me. Just like I can't. But it's like you make it 100
Speaker 332: percent.
Speaker 117: I've got more people after this, but I wouldn't take it personally. It's no.
And
Speaker 5: honestly, I love that you're a fighter. I love that you can't be bought. Regardless of how much they attack you, you won't back down. They've tried to come at you with defamation lawsuits and harassment, protective orders and stuff. And none of that will stop you. None of that will deter you. I don't know if you know about me, but I've actually...
Speaker 5: Charting Point has sent me four cease and desist already, and they have also filed two copyright strikes trying to take my channel down and silence me. Wow. And that's why I like you.
You're a
Speaker 334: lot like
Speaker 5: me because you're not willing to back down. You're willing to stand on your principles and do what's right regardless. Yeah.
Speaker 335: Yeah.
it
Speaker 335: is it's also we
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): need
Speaker 5: people like that
thank you
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): yeah and i think you have to and i tell providers all the time when i talk to them and people i say because people come to me all the time every single day and through chats and
Speaker 242: stuff like that and tell me their story and i talk to them
and
Speaker 177 (higher-pitched voice): and i and i tell them uh it's okay i will not go public with your name if you
Speaker 73: don't want me to like if i do a story but um and i also tell people
do
Speaker 73: not go public if you're afraid of retaliation because I promise you
Speaker 123: and I say that to them I promise you it will they will it will happen to you it will happen to you it's not if it will the government retaliates on
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): people it's the most interesting thing it's what really brought me to running for governor I'm like is this really happening in our state like I know life is not
fair but I had no idea that
It
Speaker 74 (higher-pitched voice): was like this, like the government retaliates against people like what is going on right now in our world that this actually happens to silence
Speaker 123: people. I just it was mind. It's it's literally mind boggling to me that this happens in our country. And so, yeah, you have to get to a place where you're OK with that and and expect it to happen because it
Speaker 243: will it will happen when you start speaking out.
Speaker 123: Yeah.
and
Speaker 243: you know
Speaker 123: it Colin you guys
Speaker 113: both know it right you both talked about it uh it happens to all of us that start speaking out so happened to the best of
us yeah
Speaker 113: free speech right it's like it's under attack today
so um you
Speaker 113: know yep and I and me and me and
Speaker 92: Colin uphold that because of Charlie Charlie pushed free speech so much and we
Speaker 339: believe it we stand
by it
Speaker 113: yeah yeah
yeah
Speaker 113: Absolutely. And it's our country. I mean, it's just it's huge, right? It's a huge thing to be able
Speaker 134: to speak. Yeah, my
Speaker 230: name is the Project Constitution for no reason. You know, the First Amendment is paramount to our Constitution. It's paramount
Speaker 5: to our Bill of Rights. And honestly, it's a God given right. It's not even it's not you. It's not a right that's given by our government. It's a
Speaker 230: it's a right that's given to us by God at birth, you
know.
Speaker 123: Yeah. Well, it's a great thing in our country to be able to talk and, and, and yeah, it needs to be, you know, permitted and encouraged and, you know, obviously not violent stuff, but violence in terms of protest violence
and
Speaker 340: stuff like that. But that, but all of that is good, you know, free speech, protest, all that.
as
Speaker 39: charlie would say they they want to say words are violence but as charlie once said words are never violence
no
Speaker 341: yeah yeah
Speaker 39: well all
right you are
Speaker 342: amazing thank
Speaker 108: you so much for your time uh this is so exciting like i had friends texting me watching and they're like wow i wasn't gonna vote but i there's a reason to now so
Speaker 344: that's very exciting it's it gives us hope so thank you - Thank you guys.
- This has been very good.
thank
Speaker 123: you so much and thank you everyone in the chats as well you can always reach out if you want to talk more i'm available i do answer the phone and i do respond so um
it's what
Speaker 134: what i'll and i'll always be like that uh even as governor i will be like that's how i so brave you are so
Speaker 345: brave
absolutely
Speaker 346: yeah yeah well thank
you
Speaker 345: guys
Speaker 348: all right yeah well
um
please
Speaker 348: share this video, especially if you live in Arizona, please share this video with your friends and your family. Yeah.
Thank
Speaker 277: you. All right, guys. Thanks so much. And I'll share it too. Thanks so much. Yeah.
Speaker 349: Thank you. All right.
Speaker 350: Thank you, Terry.
Speaker 277: Bye.
Speaker 351: Bye.
That was a great interview. I
Speaker 351: really love her. I think she's going to do great things.
Speaker 352: Angela's great too. They're a great duo.
Speaker 353: Yeah, absolutely. They do. They make a great team.
You know me, I'm
Speaker 170 (higher-pitched voice): not normally for women, but I was like they're level-headed. They know what they're talking about.
Speaker 93: They've been in business. And I was going to mention this, the fact that Terry is a recovered
Speaker 92: addict, that takes sheer will.
like
Speaker 92: absolutely very strong person to pull yourself out of that and now you're being interviewed to run for governor like that is just that's the american dream right there that demonstrates the american
Speaker 33: dream that you can fall to the lowest point in america and you can still make your way back up and now she's running for governor so i'm
very
Speaker 93: impressed i didn't know what to expect today guys and
I'm
Speaker 93: pretty blown away. I have hope. I'm walking away from this interview and I have some hope. I
am too.
Speaker 354: I would
Speaker 1: like to tell everybody out there, all of you people that feel like you don't want to vote, you feel like it doesn't matter to vote, your vote doesn't matter, both parties are corrupt or whatever. Okay, well, now you have a reason to vote. I implore you all to go out there, But, you know, if you're in Arizona, obviously, go out there and vote.
Speaker 1: go vote for Terry she can be the change that we need she can usher in that change and help get
rid of
Speaker 1: the corruption
Speaker 230: the rot within Arizona help clean up the politics
you're
Speaker 90: muted I
Speaker 355: said get
rid of
Speaker 355: these clowns
Yep, absolutely. And
Speaker 356: hopefully put Tyler Boyer behind bars where he belongs.
And I hope he's
Speaker 5: watching, by the way. I made sure to tag him on the video, so I'm sure he'll see it.
This one's for you,
Speaker 5: Tyler. We're coming for you. And
I don't
Speaker 230: mean that as a threat, like...
Speaker 230: physically threat either so don't even try that shit
you know them all
Speaker 230: right exactly anyway
so
Speaker 5: that's going to be our show guys thank you all for joining us uh i love you all i appreciate you all
and we'll see
Speaker 5: you on the next one later